hail
hail
avoid an expected to his own people you
avoid an expected to his own people you
ok with sound cried so how it's made a
ok with sound cried so how it's made a
moment and install
moment and install
soothing  be first
волкова настоящих он to be first
yourself not hands but se7en cambodia cambodia
сами не hands а se7en камбоджа камбоджа
hello guys I will tell you in Russian
привет всем ребята я расскажу на русском
if I can, that is, I did not improve the
если можно то есть я не совершенствовали
fishing line with him it will be easier to tell in
лески с ним будет легче рассказать на
English show I will present nunez in
английском показать я презентую nunez
general in general as a whole work and I want to
целом вообще в целом работу и хочу
explain how it works and how it works in the
объяснить как он работает и как будущем
future  will be implemented within the framework of this
он будет реализован в рамках этой
system, then it began with a screen for a
системы начался потом с экраном
second,
секундочку
yes, I made a dream
да сделала сон
ball and ending for a
шарик и кончая на
second, yes, now it
да секунду сейчас
can happen, I will now translate, I will
может произойти я сейчас переведу
connect.
подключусь .
on my poppy, the poppy points extension
у меня на маке расширения маки
crashed disconnect
вылетел disconnect
and I can hear I can see the screen without so
а у меня слышно я видно экран без так
and now the
а сейчас так
cryptosystem we have done is
криптосистема у нас сделано по
because we have a hidden back side and that
что у нас скрыта задняя сторона и то
is, here we have a curator level an
есть здесь у нас уровень
artist and an ordinary person
куратор художник и обычный человек
who happened to the system and wants
который произошел на систему и хочет
buy a post and, more precisely, a bet on any
купить поста и точнее ставку на любой
coin, that is, here it
монет то есть здесь с двух сторон
turns out to close the user on both sides, that
получается закрывает пользователя то
is, the buyer and directly the one
есть покупатель и непосредственно тот
who wants to issue a coin or
кто хочет выпустить монету или
directly create i want
непосредственно создать i want
to get into the profile itself,
чтобы попасть в саму
you will need to scan the qr code
профиль нужно будет отсканировать qr-код
after scanning the redirect qr code where
после сканирования qr-кода redirect где
bot where information about yourself is set in the de bot,
бот где в де боте задается информация о
that is, bio name, well, that is, the
себе то есть bio название ну то есть
login directly and after that
логин непосредственно и после этого уже
this wallet itself is already mined where
добывается сам этот кошелек где будет
all all the coins will be stored directly,
храниться непосредственно все все монеты
a link is given, that is, I click in the de
дается ссылка то есть я нажимаю в де
bot for May nummies and it throws me to drink
боте на май nummies и меня перепить
my profile page
перекидывает на страницу мой профиль
where in the future I will be able to interact in the
где будущем я смогу взаимодействовать в
form of this creation creation creative
виде это создание создание креативен
where  it warms and it will be me each
где это греет и он это будет я каждая
coin can only be issued
монета может выпускаться только
directly directly under the
непосредственно непосредственно под
sofa there it cannot take and
диван там она не может взять и
be issued just a coin by itself
выпуститься просто монета само по себе
i.e. you need some kind of yes
то есть нужна определенная какая-то да
yes that is a certain smart contracts
да то есть определенный смарт-контракты
where i am in creating an event if i  I want to
где я в создании события если я захочу
release some kind of cop on your grandmother there, the
выпуск какой-то мент на вашу бабушку там
cover
обложку
starts like on our goal, while it
начало как у на наш гол при том он
then goes to the events, so you
уходит потом в ивенты вы вам так у нас
already have a direct vote on
идет уже непосредственно голосование за
whether to accept this event or not to accept
принять ли этот ивент или же не принять
it, that is, in this case we have this  for now,
то есть в данном случае у нас это пока
it just left without any
просто оно ушло без какого-либо там
voting there, but in the
голосования но
future it will happen from the side of
будущем это будет происходить со стороны
the fact that there will be votes voting like a
того что будет голоса голосование как
google hangout, that is, for
google притон то есть за монеты
internal coins, we will not just have
внутренние у нас будет не просто
jade coins directly, for now
непосредственно монеты нефритом пока что
it will be a couple of auctions a couple of events
это будет пара аукционов пару событий
will be done on through  a contract from the
будут сделаны на через контракт со
side in a free house where it will
стороны in free доме где это будет
be thrown at the address as in a corrugated
будет закидываться на адрес как в гофре
tone, she left the vote and
тон она ушла на голосовании и пример
took the example from the conditional  talking here in my
принял из условно говоря и здесь в мои
event, I can already send my applications, that
событие я могу уже слать свои заявки то
is, there is a date from and to
есть там дата от и до
where in the interval of this I can become as a
где промежутке этого я могу стать как
regular user,
обычный пользователь
that is, we have a competition was the next
то есть у нас есть конкурс был ближайшие
two or three weeks ago
две или три недели назад где
where 111 people
подали там 111 человек
submitted their applications there with coins  that is,
заявки свои с монетами то есть на один
he says to one, that is, they will be able to
говорит он то есть они смогут
attach, press the button to take
прикрепить нажать кнопочку принять
part, change them, throws them to
участие их перешить перекидывает на
issue a coin, where the
выпустить монету где уже непосредственно
creation of the coin will be directly indicated, this is the
будет указываться создание монеты это
first one, this is the front side, the front
первая это лицевая сторона лицевая
side here will be filled up to 190 kilobytes,
сторона здесь будет до 190 килобайт
while the information is not relevant,
это пока информация неактуальна показано
everything is shown while we have  so smart, that is, we have
все пока у нас так смарта то есть мы еще
not yet attached one hundred and ninety kilo bytes to without a prog, one hundred and ninety
не прикрепили на без прог сто девяносто
kilo bytes are poured from the picture and I
кило байтов заливается с картинка и я и
replicate a certain amount with a
тиражируют какое-то количество со
starting price,
стартовой ценой
this is all according to the specification
это все по спецификации
type 31, this is Mitya that you attached to the
тип 31 это митя что прикрепил вы на
form, attention is the back side for now, but
форме внимание задняя сторона пока но
specifically in this  event, it will not
конкретно в этом ивенте она не будет
act in subsequent Ivan events,
действовать в последующих иван эвентах
it will also be an active side where
это будет тоже активная сторона где
it can be from behind  hiding on the reverse and
сзади это может скрываться на реверс и
obverse, the back side will be hidden, well,
аверс задняя сторона будет скрываться ну
information, it can be a picture there is a
информация это может быть картинка там
gif, it can be anything, and it
гифка может быть но все что угодно и она
will be available only to those who actually
будет доступна только тем кто собственно
own it, and that is, in fact,
говоря ей владеет и то есть по сути его
you will have
подождать будет вы будете что посмотреть
to wait for it to see it, you need to wait for it  action through a
его нужно подождать это действие через
direct ball,
непосредственный ball
that is, the key, in general, I issued this
то есть ключ в общем я выпустил эту
coin, the coin can only be launched,
монету монета только может запускаться
as I said under the event, that is, it
как я говорил под событием то есть это
will definitely be, that is, if I click there,
обязательно будет то есть если нажму там
participate, will it happen
поучаствуйте ли там произойдут
at the direct address anyway, at least
по прямому адресу все равно хоть
some event will be then it leaves
какое-то событие будет потом она уходит
in the marketplace,
в marketplace
well, the auction can be said as you like and
ну аукцион как угодно можно сказать и
it becomes available and
она становится доступным и
directly in the events
непосредственно в ивентах
where under the bottom there will be a list of attached
где под низом будет список прикрепленных
coins where it will be loaded, a
монет где она подгружаться будет от
list of all coins will be issued from the smart and
смарта выдаваться список всех монет и и
it will be available no longer
будет она будет доступна уже не
through the latter, here it will be the
посредства последних вот здесь будет это
last coins added  marketplace I
последние монеты добавлены marketplace я
can already with them will be shown which one on
уже могу с ними будет показана какому на
exactly pr  belongs directly to the
именно принадлежит непосредственно по
coins with which they worked to buy,
монеты которые с которой работали купить
that is, it will also be with us what
то есть это будет у нас также что
happens through we have this for an
происходить через у нас есть это на
increase, the standard fee we have created,
повышение стандартная такса у нас создан
that is, it is for an increase
то есть он на повышение
there, we still have done and lowered
там у нас еще сделано и понижения
English, but we will have the future it’s
английский но будет у нас будущем это
like  to divide by increase and
как бы делиться на повышение и на
decrease, you will choose already in the marketplace
понижение выберешь уже в marketplace
how the auction will be your own work,
как будет аукцион собственная работа это
all the information will be, well, it will all
вся информация будет ну это все
happen through the direct
происходить будет через непосредственно
addition, that is, I indicated the amount qr-code
добор то есть я указал сумму qr-код
turned out this qr-code I am not bricks, but I
выдался этот qr-код я не брики но я
confirmed the action and I  already displayed
подтвердил действие и я отобразился уже
directly in these parts,
непосредственно вот в этих частях
also if the curator invites the
также если куратор приглашает
artist, otherwise he naturally
художник а то он естественно забирается
takes some percentage of this, since he
этого какой-то процент так как он
invites the artist, this will work as a
приглашает художник это будет работать
platform, that is, he takes the curator from sales,
платформой то есть он от продаж забирает
that’s actually all if I haven’t
куратор вот собственно все если я не
forgotten anything, so thank you all  who
забыл ничего так что всем спасибо кто
heard
послышалось
and
а
thanks for your reverence sau hon soo
спасибо за твои почитающие сау хон су
bin next i han eun soo bin in this
бин next я хан ын су бин в этом
suppo construction team  rt this opens
командой стройке support this opens
nobody
nobody
olga
ольга
autumn in cipher von dmitry
осенние в шифром фон дмитрий
the blockchain database her asks where is the blockchain here the
базе блокчейн her спрашивает где здесь
whole system built on this
блокчейн вся система построенная на этом
that I didn’t understand the question what does it mean
что смысле не понял вопрос что значит
where is the blockchain smart contracts implementation
где блокчейн смарт-контракты реализации
the work with tokens itself, i.e. root
сама работа с токенами то есть рут
work the system is built directly
работа система построена непосредственно
well so why jade
ну так че нефритом
you can go see the cops guide and
можно зайти посмотреть гид копы и по
work directly with the ready-made code
работать непосредственно с готовым кодом
on the front, it’s not easy for us
именно фронте это у нас не просто там
to quickly collect it there, it’s not html made,
быстро взять собрать он не html сделан
it doesn’t repeat it, well, it takes
он не повторять это ну как бы занимает
time, as it were, to put it all together,
время это все вместе его
and to vote for this some kind of
причем на голосование за это какую-то
work  according to the tone of the event, each has its own
работу по тону event каждый имеет свою
focus, so there is some
направленность поэтому есть какой-то
important i want if some Vasya
важный i want если там какой-то вася
went to the toilet there, well, he created an
там в туалет сходил это ну и он создал
event that I went to the toilet this well,
event том что я в туалет сходила этот ну
and he can’t be, so I don’t think
и он не может быть поэтому я не думаю
that he  will accept that is, it will be
что он будет принимать то есть это будет
directly this movie and will be accepted
непосредственно это кино и приниматься
how many kvach nits
how many квач ниц
so you can and you create a contract for an hour to
так можешь и ты создать контракте час
show this address tons of liv with  now
показать этот адрес тонн лив сейчас
I can’t show candies, I
конфеты показать ничего не не могу это я
think write to me in the forest, I’ll show it and
думаю напишите мне в лес я это покажу и
tell you in more detail, I
расскажу более подробно просто у меня
just don’t have a smart contract developer with me yet,
еще нет со мной разработчика по smart
and
а
the buying and selling mechanism is located in the
механизм покупки-продажи расположен в
bag-end,
бэг-энде
maybe I posted giggit in the background on the forum
может на фоне на форуме я выкладывал
x
гиьгит х
who does not have the opportunity to vote with them
кто ими не имеет возможность голосовать
any member of the platform member of the
любой участник платформы участник
platform in this case, while
платформы в данном случае пока
voting is an hour as I said no, it
голосования час как я сказал нет это
will appear in the near future that it will be possible
ближайшем будущем появится что можно
to vote, but the unique address will
будет голосовать но уникальный адрес
sleep my Shinji tokens
засну свои синдзи токены
and
а
funk soul oxford
funk soul оксфорд
olga olga koval kintoki thing I can
кинтоки вещь могу
in Russian  to say how convenient and old the
по-русски говорить как удобно и давности
city can be mixed
город можно миксовать
into this mixes ok
в эту миксы ok
my name is olga 2 volskaya i want to
меня зовут ольга 2 вольская я хочу
thank everyone for this wonderful
поблагодарить всех за этот прекрасный
competition really very worthy applications
конкурс правда очень достойные заявки
angels to the world in the hangout ambassador contest
ангелы миру в притон ambassador contest
8 or in city spacer place which is best
8 or in city спейсер place which is best
on an old man in saint  petersburg in the
on an old man in saint petersburg in the
market place is in aftermarket isofix
market place is in aftermarket isofix
points may ambassador programs all
поинтов мая ambassador программ все
is in art space  he is a [ __ ] connections you
is in art space он калека connections вы
hall ding ding ding artist washed in rdk
зале ding ding ding артист промыла в рдк
g-power background you help beautiful
g-power background вы help beautiful
magnificent fair in october your
magnificent fair in october твой
incident we have as our
инциденте у нас качестве нашего
background creation on the theme of this weave
бэкграунда создания на тему этой плести
how this idea was born corrected wonders for
как родилась эта идея поправили чудес на
a contemporary art fair from
ярмарку современного искусства от своего
where at 20  year on the basis of our
где при 20 года на базе нашего
space, I am now in the chat throwing off a
пространства я сейчас в чат скинув
link to how she went through this
ссылочку на то как она прошла это
to show our competence in
чтобы показать нашу компетенцию по
galleries on content there further from our
галереям по контенту там дальше от наш
instagram who are interested can
инстаграм кому интересно можете
look at the owl site agreement is
посмотреть у совы сайт agreement is
connected galleries
connected galleries
about my thing on over marketplace
about my thing on over marketplace
instincts point and  for so i go to
инстинктов point and for so i идти на
peace lebanon
мир ливан
i 41 million according to a dream and
я 41 млн according to a dream and
berries
berries
you won that become history table
вы вон ту стать истории стол
physics art object you cannot be move from
физика арт-объект вы cannot be move from
[music]
[музыка]
art object soul and deal mayor skinch
арт-объект soul and deal мэр скинч
object is here in art and soul in
объект is here in art and soul in
working a photo for scan qr code season
working a photo for скан qr-код season
and any person can track from blockchain
and any person can track from блокчейн
for informations about
за informations about
owner is art object sau would stand goods
owner is арт-объект сау бы стоял товар
marke  t you became not only digital art at
market вы стал not only digital art at
all the way physics
all the way физика
art object and in rush art and i hope it
арт-объект и ин раша art and i hope it
is marked and blind selection
is marked and blind подбор по пилори
by call pylori on call collector twin peaks sau the
по вызову коллектор твин пикс сау
principle of creation of our creations the principle of the
принцип создания наши создания принцип
rally on the marketplace
митинга на маркетплейсе
curated i.e. closed as well  how
curated то есть закрыт так же как
super air works and also how
работой super air и также как работает
not all gateways work, that is, it is not a public
не все gateway то есть это не публичное
posting of works,
размещение работ
it is not about instinct, any person can
это не об инстинкте может любой человек
create such as I did, taking any
создатель таких как сделала я взяв любую
picture of my desktop,
картинку своего рабочего стола
that is, in my opinion about the boarding house
то есть на мой взгляд о пансионе
is a supplier of the quality of work and
является поставщиком качество работ а
watch you want  to create such a market
watch хочется создать такой market
that has become a supplier of quality,
которая стала поставщиком качество
respectively, together with a group of
соответственно бы вместе с группой
validators, these golds, we made a
валидаторов эти голдой о мы сделали
collaboration and created it in the market,
коллаборацию и создали в маркет
and now I would like to give the floor to
и сейчас я хотел бы передать слово
the development manager Sasha Alekseev and
руководитель разработки саша алексееву и
that he demonstrate the
чтобы он продемонстрировал
possibility of our site, if possible,
возможность нашего сайта если можно вот
give the opportunity to Alexander Alekseev,
дать возможность александра алексеева
who raised  bow now and he
который поднял лук сейчас и он
will demonstrate the possibilities and okay okay
продемонстрирует возможности и окей окей
retirement
пенсии
marketplace it's true i can see screen
marketplace it's true i can see screen
flow and confirmed
flow и confirmed
i want one and hold in
оценкам сценки а i want one and hold in
the king how to buy the king how to sell
the king how to buy the king how to sell
takin' it and speak about shorts and souls
takin' it and speak about шорты и souls
i can be taken as we have a dot
i can been taken as we have a dot
edh product  he not dev d-classes have
продукт из эдхов он не дев d-классы have
proved by searching for production and
proved by searching for production and
we create a dog's mdf for july formats
we create a dog's мдф for july форматов
for all of president
for all of president
lard no anita hill force first one to
сало нету анита хилл force first one to
select image is with my jess this view and
select image is с моими джесс этот вид и
plz
плз плз
plz mind lays basis we have  several person
на ум лайс основу we have several person
for very end of the experts will be paid
for very end of the experts will be paid
for
for
who's
who's talking and content автор издаст
talking and content  inter die from person to not
метр и к.н. интер die from person to not
max
макс
find in practice image jus in das
найти на практике имиджевыми jus in das
auto from and the court is
auto из и суда стоит онли фо
only for this test and in da house is
only for this test and in da house is
art is mine think i want to go out and
art is mine think i want to go out and
sit at
sit at
washed away
смыл
mind is talking how to buy it plays and
mind is talking how to buy it plays and
is a difference a difference
is a difference a difference на сайте
start loves bing trouble z axis i don't have
старт любит bing беда оси z i don't have
no
no забит
ngc another auction for example for
ngc another аукцион for example for
example
example
and axis starting with certain knew this
и оси starting with certain знал этот
exe
exe
think my little late several
not me think my little late several
times servants and ran you samsung
times слуги и бегал тобой samsung
ok ohman you on the axis
окей охман тобой на оси
or the link and in love and i want to
либо the link and in love and i want to
lose your phone up and get uppercut
lose your phone up and get апперкот
instruction how to get the stockings
instruction how to get the stockings
athos  files or die
тиристор аккаунт из массив files or die
for example discane anthony clouds below
for example дискейн энтони тучи ниже
se  tting student mycosis on the forehead working
сеттинг студенок микоз на лбу working
no gaining file from my football but
нет файла gaining из моего футбол а
inter in and minus
интер in and в минус ok
ok if yes here me and seed from dilapidated and
а если да вот я и сид из ветхого и
boeing and trend can buy it now
боинг и тенденция can buy it now
and i inter may world beko ce site and
а я интер май world beko ce site and
i'll be send  a young i and pensions message
i'll be send a young я и пенсии месседж
in our ideas and balls to make me how it
in our ideas and balls to make me how it
aion aion to sell or set
aion aion to sell or set
blockchain fms not than life without
и на блокчейн фмс не than life без
agency is more inside the next akin you
agency is more inside the next akin вас
took this now i want to show how the
взял этот now i want to show how the
boss from auction from you directly in
boss from аукцион from you directly in
its
its
phenomenon case directory directly to gold
феномена кейс directory directly to gold
here it is and fantasy
а еще вот вот вот а его вот он и fantasy
of rain in with the site to the cashier both its
of rain in с сайтом в кассу both its
effect buy cm and it's very me have
effect buy cm and it's very me have
several shares and on web content and z-axis
several акций и на web content and оси z
a uh not
а эм нот
full throttle contact picasso netlogon
полный газ контакт пикассо netlogon
noobs n1 usa
нубов n1 usa
worldwide in on mind disk contract it is
worldwide в на mind диск контракт it is
this  world and is in france
this world and is in france
[music
[музыка]
] this hammer is
вот этот молот
okay 7 my world
окей 7 my world
n  found talking laptop surf intimacy and
найдено talking ноуту surf интима и
we would
нам бы и
and weight in debate slow link ok in dust
and weight в дебаты slow link ok in dust
and mild
and mild
ok and axis z contract of the author name is
ok and оси z контракт автора name is
young person of the end they the price
young person of the end они the price
fox and list and operations due to made
fox and list and operations из-за сделал
there is ok and aysel
туда is ok and aysel
informations and fi south aziz and appeared
informations и фай south азиз и появился
exquisite this a i get reverse
изысканных этим а i get реверс
nexen n to marquetry vans
nexen n до маркетри vans
autoreverse they enter u token fog
автореверс они вступают у токен fog
seen behind stockings will return to one
видел за stockings will return в на один
dolphin
дельфин
they to sing resource in civil times ok
они to sing ресурс в civil таймс ok
confirm i'm full cage here i spots on u
confirm я сыт кейдж вот я пятна на у
in a hurry root contract z mind a direct
спешил рут контракт z mind a direct
contract
контракт
get internet from the boat and right to
get internet from the boat and right to
deploy
deploy
director contract and na jan fried he and they
директор контракт и на ян фрид он и они
play all i've been and i'm with deebot the check
play all i've been а я уж с deebot чек
for the contract are not alone in a block
за контракт are not alone in a block
chain address sorry i  can't copies z and
chain адрес sorry i can't копий z и
touches then narrow agent copies await you
касается то сузим агент копий await you
can write this manli anton than life
can write этой манлий антон than life
and father is contract contract
and father is контракт contract
manitou activate contract 89 of miss a and
маниту activate контракт 89 из miss a и
lind died from a
линд умершим from a
energy taking us is contract wendy's
энергий taking us is контракт wendy's
contract ende des contact and se  nse
контракт ende des contact and sense
hurry interna meat what nfpa this in
спешим интерна мясо что nfpa этим in
czech fire
czech огня
contact vape ink surf ok
контакте вейп инк сурф ok
confirm appreciate the message cost cheops
confirm ценят мессидж стоили хeопса
pro-bending astapov would have heard when there were no special stages
про-бендинг астапов слых бы когда допов
network provence ok ok enda found
нет network прованс окей-окей энда нашел
ajax z and plz is in taking place in
аяксе z и плз is in taking place in вот
these axes z apple  sensei ensure axes
эти оси z apple сенсеев ensure оси у
i have ip address from from my address
меня адрес ip с из мой адрес
ok album turbine all for jam blaze no
ok альбом turbine all for джем пылай нет
then he is from but 3 start no lags becuase i
то он от но 3 старт нет лагов becuase i
want to buy usa and called without ben for
want to buy usa и называл без бена за
client either 100 copies set phrases
клиент не то ли 100 копий set phrases
value tripod no andarza  im
значение штатив нет андарза им
settings did not enable
settings did not enable
axles and price per contract with and at the end of tetz
оси и цена за контракт с и в конце тэц
per cent you can sizo toyota aygo this will not
на цент you can сизо toyota aygo это на
count cape of the boss and white
засчитает cape of the boss and white
wine of a from can scan some and on
wine of a из can scan какого-то и на
krang tusur in this and here is up  in usa
крэнга тусур в этом и вот is up in usa
address glinks d-bot message z contents
глинки адресов d-bot message z contents
and then in dust and i want to buy and
and then in dust and i want to buy and
understand
understand
ok x-mode here asi asi with these from gray you
ok x-mode вот аси asi этим из серого
fix and Ivan you for ai wont from san
чинишь а иван тобой за ай вонт из сан
peter
питер
and if you decide with frantically talking for
а если вам решено с бешено talking for
processing  the action service is great
processing the action service is great
game pc
game pc
no
нет
blue  tez ok crysis it is not for
синтез окей crysis it is not not for
sell market place i can see all in
sell market place i can see all in
circles
circles
a dick ozon.ru is-8 f14
а хуй ozon.ru ис-8 f14 миксе
mixe insurgent in the base with ok nau ai bottles
инсургент в базы с окей нау ай bottles
and i'm happy in history
and i'm happy in history
in
я оси за той spend сванте ван talking in
the end archive rivers front called
the end архиве риверс фронт вызван
talking and blossomed out talking ford
talking и цвела из воз talking ford
transit ford transit he
transit ford transit он
find hey on redon and the families of fame
найти эй на редон и the families of fame
flour with my movie token and
муки с моей токен кино и
knysh u samsung ce
кныш у samsung ce
minutes customer cheese and plz ready son ho
минут сыр клиента и плз готовой сын хо
have an ocean star auction  ses and plunger
have an ocean star аукцион сэс и вантуз
go to go to rhythm and
отойду в отойду в ритма и
new world if fold boss sam and a i
new world если складку босс sam and a i
want us to the uk's he is ready
want us to the uk's он готов
auction to
аукцион в
is it works on minutes of words like it
is it works on минут из words like it
works like director buy we have several
works like директор buy we have several
times spa
times спа
phobos weekend offender
фобос weekend offender
mendel the five  the direction of the
мендель the five the direction of
auction by a gang of
аукцион бандой
missiles without a price delta wreath nintendo
ракеты без прайс дельта венок nintendo
in which announced the show battle and no end in
in which объявила шоу битва и no end in
usa friends format notes si kay and over there
usa френды формат ноты си кей и вон ту
went and out of you like the
ходил и из вас лайка
forces of the contract baht on for common with no
сил контракта бат на за общего с нет
with several times mein tuverta beko ce
with several times майне туверта beko ce
blog  Sanskrit then  carried ksn do if we
blog санскрита то везла ксн do if we
have a contract in this set with
have a contract in this set with
different validator locks in women's
different валидатор locks in women's
one of the meat that root contract for deep
одна из мяса что root contract for deep
hurried rub contract z heat and
спешил руб контракт z тепло и
smartq z deploy auction smart contracts
smartq z deploy аукцион смарт-контрактах
and floors
а полы
belgrade
белград
here its
вот своей
no tags watermelon beard park was itself
нет меток арбуз борода парк был сам
lacks in dub
lacks in dub
navy don't send y
вмс don't send у
and axis if in physics grade 8
и оси если по физике 8 класс
mozart don sent ok ok ok
моцарт дон sent ok ok ok
stroy stroy
stroy stroy
from is not a smoke fell it's true both its
из is not a упал дым это правда both its
time we try of dub new
раз пробуем of dub новая
intertool
intertool
it automatics in when on the test
он automatics в при на тест
catching move away and panda  on a
уловив отойду и панду на а
and putting on the club is wise that and a big as it is
и надев клуба мудр тот и a big as it is
open for all other in dust and we have
open for all other in dust and we have
hurried test chat and find out if i want to
спешил тест чат и find out if i want to
be a test
be a test
butt on the rhythm of the
бют на ритме волга
volga envy from his endore and the
envy от его эндоре и
war he is weak and named boeing  back
войну он слаб и назван боинг назад
auction
аукцион
have to be here and not extremely
have to be here and not крайне
bat hunting don't slip on all is said and
бат охоты don't slip on all is said and
i like it
i like it
my price and five days mondays resource
моего price and five days mondays ресурс
arsenka
arsenka
this atom of chromium appreciates not sitges and
этот атом хрома ценит не ситжес и
beauty
красоте
go but may be actors in active white
иди но в may be actors in active white
wine contract  beaten be deployed and
wine контракт избил be deployed и
fightin copies of this
fightin копий этой
and it will pass joaquin founder and a single
и он пройдет хоакин founder and a single
taste and olson contract asset october
вкус и олсон контракт актив октябрь
contract i tastefully there no to show how
контракт я со вкусом там нет to show how
to give belt assy
to give belt assy
and may nation
и нация
auction princeton clear killed
мая аукцион princeton ясно убит
ok this show cold as old as a bit in my
окей это шоу cold as old as a bit в моем
faukin
фокин
tones i it's easy  with shows and lags and i
tones я it's easy with шоу и лагов and i
want a
want a
magen out paladin bad i can't be kind of
магин вон паладин bad i can't be kind of
the survey
the survey а я хлоп да это диксит
flag do
флаг
yu kinsey from this sister and history
д о ю кинсей из это сестре и history
sistine here is a photo faith is a big ass and
сикстин вот фото faith is a big ass and
miles contract
miles контракт
furniture
мебель
ok alpha gola tusurov enda
ok альфа гола тусуров
in excel
в excel таймс ван ту фри
times one thu free ok vader altai ms mod beta fox on a help
вейдер алтай ms mod beta fox on a help
it up in dust and mild and  a sore and
it up in dust and mild and a sore и
fate conformation in a phase quarrel these
судьба конформация в ссоре фазы эти
minimum extent and lancer very
минимум extent and lancer очень
ah wont tu van thu free resource
ай вонт ту ван ту фри ресурс
aisin antiphon antifreeze klusmann
айсин антифон антифриз клусманн
extent of a container service
extent of a container service
was times taste and
был таймс вкус и
and current bid 33
и current bid 33
i saw you dancing and it was in the city
i saw you dancing and it was in the city
for effective  and i can help and
for effective and i can help and
functions  that may be again when you
functions that may be again when you
said digital content
said digital content
now we now we say of content in our
now we now we say of content in our
service
service
but link not in black and its very very
но link not in black and its very very
very same so many price is back as big
very same so many price is back as big
as a la
as a la contex филби из видео о big foto
contex  beko light and armor
и костных его beko свет и доспехов
content zip-lock video weight offers from
контент zip-lock видео весом offers из
marshmallow saying and essays say and to that
зефира говоря and essays говори и в ту
aza az hurry content and we can't stop &
аза аз спеша content and we can't stop &
pet in block chain veseng sides and on
pet in block chain veseng сторон и на
interface there dance and pfs systems freak
интерфейс там танец и pfs систем
info and bad i  know me by two in work in
info and bad i know me by two in work in
such a bad is not
such a bad is not не а фича на заказчик
samsung ps 1 quotes hope i haven't had
samsung ps 1 цитирует hope i haven't had
not always searching with hope taste with
not always searching with hope вкус with
a small changes in all
a small changes in all a market поест
a market fixed all do both to sing
этот продукция fixed all do both to sing
when i'll take 2 thousand beko ce
when i'll take 2 тысячи beko ce
take care of the interface and yonder screw token
заботиться интерфейс и вон ту винт токен
and productions
и на productions
soul and we test it all and i want to
soul and we test it all and i want to
mind taking in productions and not our
mind taking in productions и на не our
time by tomorrow and now we all times
time by tomorrow and now we all таймс
test mdf not be has  its very
тест мдф not be has its very
hanging out why we hold it will be great to
тусит why we hold it will be great to
sell by scary  o author
sell автор страшно автор
works in a user oil
works in a user нефти
he flitton them shelling a massage without
он флиттон их обстрел а массаж без
say cancel quoe sine hold who how
говори отмене quoe синус hold у кого how
to work here from oil and posts by quark
to work вот из нефти и posts by quark
vis-a-vis person how does not now and
vis-a-vis person how does not now and
sing about a free vol 1
sing about a free том 1
big ass  while 1 b l and c business is fine for
big ass while 1 б л и ц бизнес ладен for
gallery gallery gallery
gallery gallery gallery
it'sa and users hoopoe but a few
it'sa и юзеров удод но и несколько
ballads frit he soul we want to create
баллад фрит он soul we want to create
trouble live it is away for far de dios to the
бед live it is away for far de dios в
bushes both been the extra tone plugin is
кусты both been the extra тон plugin is
very hard for  for as we cried e-mail
very hard for for as we cried e-mail
passwords for him for enda zaikin
passwords for him for за энда заикин
laden n-th site and mind taking a yes
ладен n-ого site and mind taking a да
true form n.n.
правда форм н.н.
in this in hell forms and for and kinsey
in this in hell форм и за и кинси
for intense commission cats of chance we
за intense комиссия кошками шанса we
place in a fir without speaking for
place in a fir без говоря за кинси
kinsey galeria de dios bin laden you are
galeria de dios бен ладен вы
automatic in your ear and just about out gallery
автоматики на уху и вот-вот из gallery
and enjoy pensioner world has been in
and enjoy пенсионер world has been in
mind for put avner hair
mind for ставим авнер волосы
soul is for very easy for frozen bath
soul is for very easy for frozen bath
with lady phone from dev no beko ce
with lady phone from дев нет beko ce
jury kang min token picos
жюри кан мин токен picos
users can the mind taking in this good
users can the mind taking in this good
point for test in productions
point for test in productions
login only for glory beko ce byers
логин only for glory beko ce байерс
don't no m from world interview  i can set
don't нет м из интервью world i can set
intervals
intervals
address i and it works as it works in
адрес я and it works as it works in
which in the words in mind
which in the words in mind
apple in the pension ivan talking and
apple in the pension иван talking and
you can set any key css start auction
you can set any key css старта аукцион
if you right of rain
if you right of rain
world you can see for 100 baht you can the
world you can see за 100 бат you can the
soldiers  big as you can do so in
soldiers big as you can do so in
transaction use both with an heart
transaction use both with an сердцу
alyona ladies we help through and we stacey
алена дамы мы помогаем через а мы стейси
galleries and artist mommy climb up
галереям и художника мамочка забраться в
including launch the browser get the
том числе запустить браузер получить
addressee surf and of course us a whole
адресатом сурф и конечно же нас целая
team is dedicated to explaining  no, and
команда занимается тем что объясняет и
we work with them quite a lot, it’s not so
достаточно много работаем с ними не так
easy for old-school galleries that
просто для олдскульных галерей которые
turned out to be narrow, here the gallery owners they have a
оказались вот галеристы у них есть
great resource and respect from the community,
большой ресурс и уважение от сообщества
but they are not very well versed
но они пока не очень хорошо разбираются
in this yet, so we need help in any case
в этом поэтому нужна помощь любом случае
well if rogonda symbols and is talking
well if рогонду symbols and is talking
year sasha  arches and theirs several of cost
году саша арок и их его several of cost
you can find a person from you talking
you can find a person from you talking
in you can do usa
in you can do чем авнер usa
inter monitor all interested and the
интер monitor all interested and the
taken and small fee like Matthew Smallville
taken and small fee like матфею смолвиль
you like wonton in this month on byl by
you like вонтон in this month on byl by
a street beko ev a between  the author
a street beko ev а between автор
and nf3 contract bat yu lived on lease
и nf3 контракт бат ю жили в лизинг
ivan ivan trust with and not so red cell
иван иван траст с и не так red cell
contract enzistal contract build mind public
энзистал контракта билде виду пабликов
goats ndnd enzistal frames of us when it
коз нднд энзистал кадрах of us when it
sounds from rus for sales with this into this
sounds из rus for sales с этим into this
you and ownership to sell contract and
you and ownership to sell контракт и
hurry this  background and the third land of the
спешим этот фон и третьим land of the
ship is like sex with oh
ship is like секс с ой
and sit run playful is like you change
и сидите ран playful is like you change
management for you talkin to the talking
management for you talkin to the talking
you
you
kung fu manager comments you talkin to
менеджер кунг-фу comments you talkin to
and on z  and the contract buy time is it and gave
и на за контракт buy time is it and gave
a worse than this is the end if the owner of
a worse than this is the end if owner of
a keen keen
a keen keen
icosahedrons and the convenience of the stations is good well
икосаэдров и удобство станций хорошо ну
then we need to give the other
тогда нам нужно дать возможность другим
participants the opportunity to show the platforms too
участникам тоже показать платформы
so then we
поэтому тогда мы и
i hope you can go to the devs blu  bumble
i hope you can go to у дев blu bumble
bee and commentary on buy the ocean
bee and commentary on buy the ocean
in braids xml baxi
в косах xml baxi
deus ex is bad love i show you its
deus ex is bad love i show you its work
work 2nd place of bad at school
и в к сайтам 2nd place of bad at school
of rock you can i buy up and have you
of rock you can i buy up and have you
buy a
buy a
forehead and talking in may not  wish it and
лба и talking in may not wish it and
then get an engine sound forge have
then get an engine sound forge have
limited time and latex 500 shields per novel
limited time and latex 500 шиты за роман
ambient novel
ambient роман
nuts i s novel g.na
орехи я с роман g.na
from our school in all over and end up
from our school in all over and end up
in a small 1000 baht
in a small 1000 бат
combined contex will consist of filth in
совмещен contex will consist of filth in
his plans  and sound was taking all
his plans and sound was taking all
things just because it ended
things just because it ended
uyar intern in most technical
уяр intern in most технику
sites
сайтах
warm up technical solution and aid in
грейтесь technical solution and aid in
bed technical sing and smoky tired and was
bed technical поют и дымно устал и был
andy space saving
энди space saving
of
власти из снг на нтв рен тв angels of
contentsar  e always
contents are always
baht to strength rest crawled
бат до силы отдых проползал
ndnd life it was on your
нднд life это был на твой
me by one man's game
me by one man's игру
url from coat of arms for a mile crawl
url с герба за милю проползу
floor stepp tsar ivan bout nfc
пол стэпп царь иван bout nfc
these zones fian forum tekken 2 million until
эти зоны форум фиан tekken 2 млн до
retirement
пенсии
interpol ender marketplace with ndnd fight and
интерпол эндер marketplace с нднд бой и
invite his years vat  corners
инвайтом его лет ндс углы
ambient for users
ambient for users
if i want you got you can also see give
if i want you got you can also see даст
hive date ice baby
ульем дату ice baby
urvan exit g uid nikita monks and
urvan выйти г uid никита монахов and
media garage rdd
media гараж рдд
n.d.
н.д.
it calls sound like us web development
it calls sound like нам web development
and
and sand да и в самом высшем собаки
sand i can ask me and i will tell you more and i can tell
иван i can ask me and i will tell
you more
you more
expo in this small player
экспо in this small player
file systems
file systems
this is blockchain in the plant
это блокчейн в в plant
and pfs and in box life ft
и pfs and in box life ft с этим поселком
character of tanks
character of tanks
indesit tan tan
indesit tan tan lines
lines no content in in fresh step son
месте нет content in in fresh step son
like a token of the mad when you decided
like a token of the mad when you decided
ti1 blockchain and descent  for example
ti1 блокчейн и descent for example
[music]
[музыка]
waiter students you
официант учениц ты
canvas content and soul you
холст content and soul вы
one place
одном месте
shafts discount sale for example if i on
валы discount sale for example if i on
this post
this post
nominations for your forehead on the turnstile
номинациях на твой лоб на турникет
content you were over publish the site is
контент вы был над publish the site is
you think it went to the marketplace
you think it ездили на marketplace
a whole landing it will come from  mdf and chipboard with
целый десант он приедет из мдф и дсп с
others
др .
and the last fight of technical
and the last fight of technical
assured the diver seconds
уверил секунд дайвера
and done then get any
а done then get any
explain this bad viking fine
explain this bad viking fine
diagrams and combined and riff vat in whole
диаграмм и совмещен и риф ндс в целый
to admin synergy
до админ синергия
x simple seconds and had diagrams and
x simple секунд и имел диаграмм и в
don't and dice cement itself
don't and dice цементе
you can ask me a  Aleksey Polyakov hu from n
you can ask me a алексей поляков ху из n
out of dice dice Sablin he brought help
out of dice dice саблин он вывел help
you battle and content for completing all
you battle и content for completing all
actions collection for as it is a simple the
actions collection for as it is a simple
only one from and it works with main
единственный от and it works with main
no
нет
and rich
и навар
browser yandex
браузер яндекс
a whole set of competencies
целый набор компетенций
[music]
[музыка]
action slacks
action slacks
and give  sat down this morning
и дают нынче утром сел
you think you can buy
you think you can buy
nfc tags are at each
nfc tags are at each
in beijing and games and big difference
в пекин и games and big difference
between
between
author n d r and d pfff this is a single
автор н д р и д пффф this is a single
come discounts for example
прийти discounts for example
january was output unity these
января был выход unity эти
put on cell
put on cell
nfc n.d.  hive york and they will vs
nfc н.д. сам куст york and they will vs
any
люб
no self and work in this is often
нет сам and work in this is often
crate came orenburg select your own
crate приехал оренбург select your own
collection of space and it works like
collection of space and it works like
verossa user beijing and collection of this
verossa user пекин и collection of this
in his own and this cd we will find the
in his own and this cd мы найдем
html you perceived without
html вы восприняли без
lowering the height  and
опущен высоты и
pictures in the pictures may be very
pictures in the pictures may be very
siege content content
осаде контента content
indian under best you
индийский под лучшая вы
they stand dt on deacon test
они стенд dt на дикон тест
content first in in this matter place to
контент first in in this matter place to
bed wars main thing of market place you
bed wars main thing of market place you
can see for example
can see for example
at sense of paper artist in lcl
на адрес sense of paper artist в lcl
derek  the bar itself
дерек сам баре
the us dollars for if
the us dollars for if
over films the artist was here
над films артист был тут
facebook he ate
фейсбук он съел
[music]
[музыка]
over people will increase by his
над people will increase by свой
despite his soul and we decided they
despite his soul and we decided they
decided
decided
aur main thing is in a market place will
aur main thing is in a market place will
be taught in collections with the parks
be taught in collections with the parks
and good
and good
sadness of the island of maui raffia
печаль острова мауи рафию
and you concert in the marketplace this
и ты концерт в marketplace это
ussr deface sign up antonin
дефейс сайн ап антонин
avanti sits and master the skill you her 100
avanti сидит и освоить навык вы ее 100
million pass enter n chipboard and mdf with it he
млн пасс войти н дсп и мдф с этим сам
started
принялся
[music]
[музыка]
cute son
милый сын
in the grea  t extent and f you now without
in the great extent and f вы теперь без
applications on you on you
applications на вы на вы
high in yandex fight point during the
высоким в яндекс fight point during the
football
football
you go there enderal sowie die and break it
вы туда enderal sowie die and break it
and designs of your profile and profile
and designs of your profile and profile
settings bow and browser avant say no
settings лук и на браузер avant say no
to some decent amount of edith
to some decent amount of edith
yourself  h and end game collections epson
сам эйч и конце игры collections epson
blockchain and zion and sons epiphysis forex
блокчейн и цион and sons эпифиз форекс
ampoules
ампулы
this plug dr high turrets out and
этот штекер д-р высоко башенки из и
ends at end
концы в конце
petr i can see his paige and z
петр i can see his пейдж и z
come from collections n.d.
прийти от collections н.д.
you tiered and beating clear language
вы ярусах и побив ясным языком
sectional gps power plant chair
секционных gps power plant chair
without file your vikings leather collection
без файл свою викинги leather collection
and diaries
and diaries
collection and jackets here he sowed
collection и пиджаки вот он сеял
here from items at emc
вот из items at emc
[music]
[музыка]
face
лицом
inbrowser
inbrowser
see from context
см от контекста
1 kinsey ndnd stable balcony
1 кинси нднд стабильный балкончике
balcony
балкончик
n.d.
н.д.
it allows you to sell or buy
it allows you to sell or buy
nfc because of nfc
nfc из-за nfc
santin like nfc here is 20 cm per year no where
сантин лайк nfc вот 20 см в год не где
man picture and it and decided
человек picture and it and decided вы
upgrade the one
for example for art and upgrade the one
last great
last great
himself merry merry and take part in the
сам merry merry and take part in the
singing and business one place
singing and business one place
ratner boris pankin was
ратнер борис панкин был
and
а
these handbags presentation novel
эти сумочки presentation роман
can I next speak just I
могу я следующему выступить просто меня
don’t need of course the
не надо конечно
test he is beautiful and was not inertia
тесту он красиво и не был собой инерции
how to gain the novel is rude from  Internet and
how to gain роман грубит из интернета и
Dmitry Kachka is asking why he is on board bayans theology of the legs and her baltabay oil you plugin why I
балтабай нефти вы plugin почему я не
can’t buy and talking elevators without a plugin
могу купить и лифты talking без плагина
but the flags well ok I’ll probably
а вот флаги ну окей я наверно по-русски
answer in Russian from no one against no the very
отвечу из никто не против нет сама
possibility it exists
возможность она существует
here the idea is exclusively product-oriented, yes, that
тут идея исключительно продуктовая да то
is, as far as the interface itself should
есть насколько сам интерфейс должен это
allow it from the point of view,
позволять с точки зрения
probably from the point of view of the platform itself,
наверное с точки зрения самой платформы
and it’s very profitable because, well, the platform
и очень выгодно потому что ну платформа
should receive its own  and comics,
должна получать свои комиксы
but in reality, in reality, you
но в реальности в реальности вы спокойно
can easily use where bots or
можете воспользоваться где ботами или
other things are to
прочими штуками для того чтобы
acquire all these things on the blockchain,
приобрести это все дела на блокчейне
since everything works to receive, in
поскольку все работает на получение в
principle, yes, there is absolutely no
принципе да абсолютно нет никакой
difference whether to buy it through the platform
разницы купить его это через платформу
or not, another question is whether he wants
или нет другой вопрос том что хочет ли
as if the platform itself, as some kind of
как бы сама платформа как какой-то
business unit, is the ability to deliver,
business unit это возможность доставлять
therefore, the question is debatable, and it
поэтому вопрос дискуссионный да и больше
depends more on the platform, plus
зависит от платформы плюс ко всему сразу
I’ll say right away that yes, and they are the first on the bird,
скажу что да и на птичке они ведь первые
so no one bothers to send them immediately to
поэтому никто не мешает их тут же
anyone, but again, this is
переслать кому угодно но опять же это
possible  when it will happen
возможно при будет происходить за
outside the platforms we will look there at
рамками платформ мы посмотрим там на
well-known examples give
известные примеры дать мне можно
me different attitudes there warmly
по-разному относиться там тепло
considerable they understandably
considerable они понятное дело базовых
restrict basic users functionally
юзеров ограничивает функционально
talkin' buy now
talkin' купить сейчас
talking how here I am now buy a
talking как вот я стою сейчас купить
token how can I buy i.e.
токен как можно купить то есть что-то
do something  and I can’t, that is, it is
сделать и не могу то есть он
registered, but is it necessary to
регистрируется но надо ли ганса
actually poke Hans  m there are stocks
собственно говоря тыкнуть там есть стоки
for which for sale and which have a
на которые на продажи и у которых есть
price there are only some not for sale
цена есть только некоторые не на продаже
and well, respectively, the dough for the sale of
и ну соответственно тесто на продаже
things on the rack
штучек дыбу
or that they are all there on the site will be
или что они там все на сайте будет
further completely continued even
дальнейшее полностью продолжение даже
showed a lie color phrase just for
показал ложью цвет фразу только бы
your advice yes well for now I  at the
совету вашего да ну пока я на данный
moment, yes, this is how it works,
момент да это так работает к сожалению
unfortunately, we didn’t have time to complete the
вот мы немножко не успели доделать
integration with the expert a little, but soon it
интеграцию с экспертом но скоро это
will be, but through extinction after 42 on
будет а вот через extinction через 42
foot,
пеший
but then,
но потом
in fact, the key problem here is the
на самом деле ключевая проблема здесь
integration of the extension, it is that at the
интеграции extension она в том что на
moment there is no there is
данный момент нету нету
no  some specifications in 3 lite
какой-нибудь спецификации в 3 lite
connection and many made an extract there
connection а многие сделали там экстракт
, for example, Brooks made this story,
он например бруксу сделали этой истории
we made this story, but for everyone it is
мы сделали эту историю но у каждого она
very different, I would like to
очень разные хотелось бы каким-то
somehow write a system that will
образом писать систему который будет все
support the whole thing, but at least three
это дело поддерживать но хотя бы три
wallets and the Socialist-Revolutionaries, therefore  it
кошелька да и эсеров поэтому это
takes some time we
занимает некоторое время мы над этим
are working on it further time it will be
работаем дальше время это будет
fixed and I will add modestly drive my
исправлено и добавлю скромно водить свою
i am fine  oh, I understand that, yes, actually
я прекрасно это понимаю да собственно
easy, we faced the same problem
easy вот с такой же проблемой
at that moment when
сталкивались на тот момент когда вообще
there were no opportunities to throw this thing at
не было никаких возможностей это дело
all, so we are working on
прокинуть поэтому-то мы работаем над
it and Saturday will be processed through
этим и суббота будет обработать через
debate, probably depending on what was the purchase in the
дебаты вероятно смотря что был покупка в
sense of the plans and will be before the purchase
смысле в планах и будет до покупку
there are plans, yes, of course,
планах есть да конечно либо для
either there is a plan for the platform, but it seems to
платформа тоже план есть но он как бы
exist, but not fully functional,
существует но не не полнофункциональный
thanks for the presentation, the presentation is very
спасибо за презентацию презентации очень
impressive, and the rest are just
впечатляющая а остальные просто время
very limited time, so I would like to
очень сильно ограничена поэтому хотел бы
give the floor to
дать слово
Alexander Stars at the center, yeah, because
александр звезды на центер агась ибо
if no one minds, I'll  Russian I
если никто не возражает я по-русски я
hope that this will save
надеюсь что это немножко сэкономить нам
us all a little time can you give me a demonstration of the
время всем а можно мне дать демонстрацию
edits my screen can be seen yes with a lemon
правок мой экрана видно да с лимончиком
yes excellent good now and so I
да отлично хорошо сейчас и так я
imagine the command to and file and
представляю как бы команду на и фай и я
I actually want to
на самом деле сейчас хочу
demonstrate the capabilities of the
продемонстрировать возможности той
platform that we have developed  but I
платформы который мы разработали но я
offer everyone right now
всем предлагаю прямо сейчас целование в
real-time kissing of their own
режиме реального времени собственных
participate in testing i.e. you
участвовать в тестировании то есть вы
can buy create a token recoup
можете купить создать токен окупить
put it up for sale optional
выставить его на продажу опционный ли
fast chopper against the corresponding
быстрый чоппер против соответствующего
token platform address is very simple on and
токина адрес платформ очень простой на и
fight .
fight . club
club right now you can go in and if
вот прямо сейчас можете зайти и если у
you have
вас есть
rubies on yours, you have
рубинчики на вашем есть у вас
an extra tone extension installed, if
установлена экстра тон расширение если
you have rubies left, then you are fully
вы остались рубинчики то вы полностью
functional in order to
работоспособным для того чтобы вместе со
test all this with me, which means that
мной все это протестировать значит что
in general our developments, as it were, I am a
касается вообще наши как бы разработки я
little bit there now  a couple of theoretical words,
немножко сейчас там пару слов
relatively speaking, we
теоретических условно говоря мы
spent a lot of time on, let's
потратили очень много времени на скажем
say, finalizing the understanding of how
так доработкой понимание того как вообще
serial tee tokens should work
должны работать серийных ти токены
in general; firstly, we introduced such a
во-первых мы внесли такой создали такой
new instance, called a manager, that
новый instance'у называется менеджер то
is, in addition to the UN rodok,
есть помимо оон родоки на
we have a manager, a manager, this is a temporary
нас есть менеджер менеджер это временный
owner  a dock on which he receives the right to
owner доке на который получает право
manage the token for a while and after that
управления токина на время и после этого
if there and after
если там и после этого
that after some time he
по истечении некоторого времени он
loses these Jews these powers and then
теряет эти евреи эти полномочия и тогда
the management powers are
полномочия по управлению вновь
returned again by the morning, respectively, the
возвращается к утру соответственно
manager of the token can be, for example, an
менеджером токина может быть например
auction and so on, that is,
аукцион и так далее то есть
respectively, if  I passed the auction
соответственно если я передал в аукцион
talkin' to he upra  it is an auction
talkin' to он управляется аукционным
if the auction, for
если аукцион
example, did not end in any way and there was
допустим никак не завершился и не был
no transaction, then it is automatically
никакой сделки то он автоматически
canceled and the right is again returned
аннулируется и право опять возвращаются
to the hands of the stones,
к он рук камни
then we use a special, as it were,
далее мы используем специальную как бы
identification of the tokens, it consists in the
идентификацию токенов она заключается в
following, we delegate the addresses of the tokens
следующем мы делегируем адреса токенов
based on the ID of the token in the hand and plus the
исходя из айди токина в руке и плюсом
address  root what follows this what it
адрес рута что за этим следует что это
gives this gives that we can calculate the
дает это дает то что мы можем вычислить
address of the tokin without regard to the graph and
адрес токина без безотносительно графу и
we need graphics and to calculate this
нам нужен графику и чтобы посчитать этот
address, that is, we can immediately count and
адрес то есть мы сразу можем считать и
can immediately go conditionally speaking there in
сразу можем зайти условно говоря там в
that live and see what is there at all
том live и посмотреть что там вообще
happens with this why it is very important
происходит с этим почему это очень важно
why because the performance of the
почему потому что производительность
graph or it is limited and,
графу или она ограничена и
accordingly, where we make a lot of
соответственно где мы делаем очень много
requests in order to parse
запросов для того чтобы раз парсов там
transactions and tokens there
транзакции и токены
and, accordingly, here we
и соответственно здесь мы очень сильно
save a lot on this whole process
экономим на всем этом процессе что
with regard to
касается
the platform itself and in general conceptually
сама платформа и вообще концептуально
like that is a night club it is
как то есть night club он
being developed by this platform  but it is
разрабатывается эта платформа
being developed as some
разрабатывается как некоторые
universal place
универсальное место
for the nav institute of a different nature
для институте nav разного характера то в
, including, for example, now we have it
том числе например сейчас у нас
implemented, that is, it’s just pictures,
реализован то есть это просто картинки
let’s call it the artwork and
назовем the artwork и
tickets, let’s start here as without
билеты давайте вот я начну как без
tickets, because probably
билетов потому что наверное
with tickets everything is more or less
с билетами все в той или иной степени
like-  then we talked, let's say we
как-то пообщались мы скажем так
crossed paths because tickets for the anniversary feast
пересеклись потому что билеты на пиру
[music]
[музыка]
free tones were made just by us and it
free тона делали как раз мы и это
was done through and through and we are now I'm
делалось вот через и бота и мы сейчас я
just perry for the heat and the lady of the bot you
мы просто перри за тепло и леди бота вы
can all test the address run
можете все протестировать адрес бегут
jesus will be able to drop in  chat for a
иисусе смогут сбросить в чат на
second so I lost where to
секундочку так я потерял где нужно
do where you can drop it into the chat I won’t
сделать где можно сбросить в чат не буду
do it on him in the chat you can drop it in the chat
это делать на его в чат можешь чат
path it’s given for another second
тракте скинуть она дана еще секундочку
now I’ll check
сейчас я проверю
yes everything is correct I’m not mistaken here
да все правильно я не ошибся вот
accordingly you can pick up from hell
соответственно вы можете забрать из черт
oil created the address of the debate  right now
нефти создала адрес дебаты прямо сейчас
it's real-time by
его в режиме реального времени по по
thousands now you can see no hit here,
тысяч сейчас видно ни под удар вот
look we launched a hundred thousand
смотрите мы запустили там сто тысяч
tickets there
билетов
minimum  the price is a whole tenth of a
минимальная цена на целых одна десятая
tone, I bought myself one ticket and now I
тона я купил себе один билет и сейчас я
will repeat the purchase again, that is, I
повторю ещё раз покупку то есть у меня
have ticket number 1, but I will return to the
есть билет номер 1 но я вернусь в
main menu and buy the
главное меню и куплю чё денги лет всем
well-known password for the safe and start
известный пароль от сейфа и запускаю
now in a few seconds transactions will come
сейчас через несколько секунд придет
accordingly, I hope a transaction will come
транзакции соответственно надеюсь придет
and it will tell me that I bought
транзакция и она мне скажет что я купил
which ticket of such and such a number and,
которой билет такого-то номера и
accordingly, give a few seconds already,
соответственно дайте уже немножко секунд
we will wait, I hope that now it’s
мы подождем я надеюсь что сейчас это
fast work Yes, I have two edemas, then
быстро работы да у меня два отёки то
there are ninety-nine thousand
осталось девяносто девять тысяч
nine hundred ninety-seven packages left,
девятьсот девяносто семь пакетов по всей
apparently field  I bought another ticket and
видимости field купила еще один билет и
I have tickets number 1 and 2, respectively,
у меня билета номер 1 и 2 соответственно
in general, this story with tickets is very
вообще эта история с билетами она очень
productive
продуктивная
and we are now working on a kind of commercial
и мы сейчас работаем как бы коммерческую
implementation
реализацию
for now, the primitive logic of these
на сейчас примитивную логику этих
tickets can be superimposed by a very
билетов может накладываться очень
complex logic
сложная логика
or pricing matrix, and for example,
или матрица ценообразования и например
that is, you can sell tickets  and there, on
то есть можно продавать билеты и там на
real tents, there are
реальные тенты там с рядом с местом
standing recumbent walk-through balconies next to the place
стоячие лежачие проходные балконные так
etc., similar, that is, all the attributes or
далее подобное то есть все атрибуты или
some kind of complex matrix, these places
какая-то сложной матрицы на эти места на
can always be superimposed on these pellets and there
эти пеллеты всегда может быть наложена и
can be a rather complicated pricing logic there
может быть достаточно сложная логика там
, that is, for example, a
ценообразования то есть например
fixed price, this price is
фиксированная цена этом цена которая
determined at the last moment
определяется последний момент
, taking into account demand, and so on.  it’s
с учетом спроса и так далее то есть это
all realizable and it’s very promising,
все реализуемо и это очень перспективное
I’m focusing on this simply
я акцентирую на этом внимание просто
because now she doesn’t associate these currents
потому что сейчас она эти токи на
with pictures, but the application
ассоциируется с картинками но применение
to these currents is much wider and much more
на эти токи на гораздо шире и гораздо
interesting, maybe let’s get back to the
интереснее может быть давайте вернемся к
pictures on the high club, that is, the start
картинкам на high club то есть стартовая
page
страница
we don’t  we were working on, let’s say, a
мы не прорабатывали как бы скажем так
large number of interfaces, we were now
большое количество интерфейсов мы сейчас
engaged in more technological
занимались больше технологическими
things, and therefore it was important for us to
вещами и поэтому для нас было важно
implement transactional things and
реализовать транзакционные вещи и
operational things, so there
операционные вещи поэтому интерфейсов
will be much more interfaces, now we
будет гораздо больше вот сейчас у нас
have could you have these pages there, let’s say
есть мог вы это страниц там допустим
activities, it’s clear that there will be
activities понятно что здесь будет там
various operations there  transactions various
различные операции транзакции различные
filter  we are on a transaction, that is, there is a
фильтры на транзакции то есть там
creation of a sale, and so long ago, like
создание продажу и так давно подобно
now, we just, within the framework of the competition again,
сейчас мы просто в рамках опять же
concentrated on the basic
сконцентрировались на базовом
functionality that can be implemented and
функционале который можно реализовать и
needs to be implemented,
нужно реализовать
so we have several tokens and you
вот у нас есть несколько токенах и вы
can see that here on some of them
видите что здесь на некоторых из них
there are some marks there  over time,
какие то есть меточки там со временем
these marks
эти меточки
are if we point to a site about cinema, here
они если мы наводим на сайт о кино здесь
there are hints of what is happening here
возникает подсказках что происходит вот
32 minutes 59 seconds this is the time after
32 минут 59 секунд это время через какой
which the
который истекает
option expires for this current, well, let's
опцион вот по данному токи ну давайте мы
go to this token and see what we
перейдем в этот токен и посмотрим что у
have,
нас
we see what we have  by the
мы видим что у нас нет ни одного не
way, in order to log in here, in
кстати в чтобы залогиниться в сюда по
fact, you don’t need any lag
сути дела не нужно никакого лагина
to log in here, except that
чтобы залогиниться сюда кроме того что
now the account must be activated at the moment, the
сейчас в моменте должен быть активирован
extruder is free, we are
аккаунт уволит экструд он волен у нас
automatically
автоматически происходит
identified, now the site has determined
идентификации вот сейчас сайт определил
what I am for  that I have an active account
что я за что у меня активен аккаунт
that ends with 87 38 we
который заканчивается на 87 38 у нас
now hardcoded
сейчас захардкожены
this rubenchik  up it is hardcoded in
этот рубенчик вверх он захардкожены в
principle then when we are in we so want to
принципе потом когда мы в мы так хотим
fill in the full version here it will be
зальем полноценную версию здесь будет
here it will be accordingly .
здесь будет соответственно .
here it will sort of differ the main, by
здесь будет как бы различаться the main
the way, donna rubies, and so on,
это кстати рубины donna и так далее
now rubies are hardcoded here, and we,
сейчас здесь захардкожены и рубины и мы
that is, the site understands that I am
то есть сайт понимает что я залогинен
logged in with such and such a wallet and associates
вот с таким-то кошельком и ассоциирует
all my operations with this wallet, if I
все мои операции с этим кошельком если я
log into my account, then I  I can
зайду в свой аккаунт то я могу его
set it up accordingly, but setting up
настроить соответственно но настройка
this account doesn’t, let’s say, not affect
этого аккаунта не скажем так не влияет
the day the person’s ability on this
на день способность человека на этом
site, I can now let’s
сайте я могу сейчас допустим
rename myself and fat, we must be
переназвать себя и жирные мы должны быть
unique and I’ll try it now for
уникальны и я сейчас попробую его за
raving, so I did it, that is,
бредить вот у меня получился то есть
now I’m right on the fly  so to speak
сейчас я сразу на лету так сказать
, the
поменялось в
username has changed and it has changed, it’s not a problem if
username и он поменялся не проблема если
I now want to do some kind of operation
я сейчас хочу сделать какую-то операцию
to carry out the operation, for example, another
провести операцию вот например другой
user owns this current to us, he
пользователь владеет этим токи нам он
announced the auction
объявил аукцион
option is valid and I can make a bit
опцион действующий и я могу сделать бит
and I just press the T-shirt bit and the
а я просто нажимаю майка бит а
minimum unit price is a
минимальная цена единицы
step  half I do let's say 2
шаг половинка я делаю допустим 2
set and send the bit I
устанавливаем и отправляю бит у меня
get accordingly I am asked 210
возникает соответственно меня просят 210
to translate the extract  he tells me about
перевести экстракт он мне говорит об
it and sends confirm the
этом и отправляемое подтверждаю
transaction, you warn me
транзакцию меня предупреждаешь у меня
to touch anything
ничего трогать
[music]
[музыка]
so we have changed
вот и у нас появилась изменилось
accordingly here in the center of the screen and
соответственно здесь в центре экрана и
I hope it can be seen we have appeared that we
надеюсь это видно у нас появился что у
have one bitter this is me the current
нас появился один биттер это я текущей
pizza is 2 and accordingly  if
пиццы составляет 2 и соответственно если
I am now, as it were, very simple, I just change the
я сейчас как бы очень простым я поменяю
user in the wallet,
просто юзера в кошельке
I changed ezra and now I act on
я поменял и эзры и теперь я действую от
behalf of another user, I make a different
имени от другого юзера я делаю другой
view, the minimum price means 2, I will leave,
вид минимальная цена значит 2 я оставлю
let's say 3,
допустим 3
again a warning that I
опять же предупреждение о том чтобы я
should not touch anything with us  there are certain
ничего не трогал у нас есть определенные
problems, as it were, with joint operations,
проблемы как бы с совместным операций
sometimes they are not performed, unfortunately,
иногда они не выполняются к сожалению
this is all for testing for verification,
это все для тестирования для проверки
so we try to warn users
поэтому мы стараемся предупреждать юзеры
so that he, let's say, carefully operates
чтобы он скажем так аккуратно оперировал
when performing these operations so that they
при выполнении этих операций чтобы они
really take place, here we have
реально которые проходили вот у нас
a second hip and the current price is
появился второй бёдер и текущей цена
3  .doc then let's go back to
3.doc тогда вернемся давайте к
something else with us besides the
чему-нибудь другому у нас помимо
auction respectively  option mode prohibits
аукциона режим опционов запрещает
receiving any other scams, if
получать какие-то другие афера если у
we have some kind of torkin not in option mode,
нас не в режиме опциона находится
then accordingly you can
какой-то торкин то соответственно можно
create another offer and here you can
создать другой оффер и здесь вот видно
see in this case I am now the
вот в данном случае я сейчас являюсь
owner of this
собственником вот этого
token, that is, I am logged in under that
токена то есть я залогинился под тем
account  according to the
аккаунтом по тем
wallet that is recognized as the
кошельком который распознается как
creator, or rather, in this case, the
создатель вернее в данном случае
owner is sinking, but in this case, the
владелец топим но в данном случае
creator is, accordingly, I
создатель вот соответственно я сейчас
can now either accept the
могу либо акцептовать
current active bit, or rather offer, I
текущей активный бит вернее offer
apologize, it means in the amount of two tones,
извиняюсь значит в размере двух тонов
or I can form an option, let
либо я могу сформировать опцион давайте
me try to accept the
я попробую акцептовать
offer,
offer
I pay a small commission
я плачу небольшую комиссию
I pay a commission for 2 transactions I pay
я плачу комиссию за 2 транзакции я плачу
for the transfer of control, which means to the
за передачу управления значит контракту
offer contract as a manager first and then
оффера как менеджеру сначала и потом
I pay a commission, respectively, when
плачу комиссию соответственно при
selling
продаже
, we’ll wait a bit, the owner has changed, that
у нас поменялся собственник несет то
is, it’s very convenient how it turns out in the interface
есть это очень удобно как в интерфейс
on one page, I immediately
получается на одной странице я сразу
see everything, as it were  dynamics of change,
вижу все как бы вот динамику изменения
that is
то есть
crater has not changed and the owner has changed
crater не изменился и сменился
and stumbled offer
собственник и споткнулся offer
accordingly collided operas now I
соответственно столкнулся оперы теперь я
can do operas as not the owner
могу делать оперы уже как не собственник
yes here
да здесь
for a second, respectively, and here we
соответственно на секундочку и вот мы
see in activities on the tokens page
видим в activities в на страницу токены
we directly see the transaction here it is 1334
мы прям видим транзакцию вот она 1334
ownership transfer here a small
переход собственности здесь небольшой
vacuum us here  instead of
вакуум нас здесь вместо того чтобы
showing the address of the owner, it
показать адрес владельца здесь
simply indicates the address of the token itself,
указывается просто адрес самого токина
this we will fix it soon,
это мы это мы поправим скоро
but the very essence and it is important here was the creation
но сама суть и важно здесь было создание
only for today in 1136
только на сегодня в 1136
now in 1334 there was a
сейчас в 1334 произошла произошло
change in the owner's rights, in fact,
изменение прав собственника вот
as if the main functionality is
собственно как бы основной функционал
now one more small thing  one more
сейчас еще одна маленькая вещь еще одна
little thing, respectively, now I’m
маленькая вещь соответственно сейчас я
right for the news lags important to
правильно за лаги news важным
log in let’s fix the account
залогиниться подправим аккаунтом
I’m now logged in under the account of
я сейчас залогинился под аккаунтом
the owner of this token
соответственно собственника этого токена
and I can, in addition to selling, I can just
и я могу помимо продажи я могу просто
stop drowning there now I’ll
перестать топим там сейчас я скопирую
just copy some other address
просто какой другой адрес
and I’ll just send it I pay a small
и я просто перешлю я про плачу небольшой
so we are waiting a little bit for the transfer of Tokin and
физа перевод токина так немножко ждем и
we have changed the owner, that is, I
у нас поменялся собственник то есть я
sent this one to another user and he
отправил эту другому юзеру и он
accordingly
соответственно
became the owner for free, that’s
стал собственником за бесплатно вот
actually, as it were, in terms of functionality, it means
собственно как бы по функционалу значит
that here you can just add more, but
здесь только что можно еще добавить но
we’ll come back again, we have them,
вернемся еще раз у нас есть они
respectively, the page I’m on
соответственно страница я на
customizable page, respectively, of the
кастомизируемый странице соответственно
participant,
участника
so here we will then add
так юзера здесь мы потом дополним
some profile
соответственно там какими-то профильными
photos of Toronto, respectively, there, let’s say for
фотографиями торонто допустим для
photographers, the description of his biography
фотографов описанию его там биографии
there is not so further, now everything is done here
уже не так далее сейчас здесь все сделал
quite simply, we have
достаточно по простому у нас есть
token galleries where you can see here we have a goal,
токена где видно вот у нас гол
that is
ну то есть
fraud, we see activity for some
махинацию видим активности по каким-то
currents, for example, here we see that
токи нам например здесь вот видим что
here the auction is also an option
здесь аукцион здесь еще тоже опцион
here offer it will still be valid
здесь offer он будет еще действительно
there for 1 hour 22 minutes we immediately
там течение 1 часа 22 минуты мы сразу
see here it means best offer two tones
видим здесь значит best offer два тона
here unfortunately also a small bug, that
здесь к сожалению тоже маленький баг то
is, this  the quantity is not here, of course, not
есть это количество здесь нет конечно не
in tones, measurement, but in active people  th
в тонов измерение а в людях активных его
Feb 1 somewhere here,
фев 1 где-то здесь вот
but at the auction there are no
только на аукционе пока нету никаких
active views yet, respectively, this is the
активных видов соответственно это
main one, as well as the functionality that I would like to
основной как и функционал что я хотел бы
add just to everything, in any
добавить просто которую ко всему в любом
case, we are now, although we have integrated
случае мы сейчас хотя мы интегрировали
so much now, in an extra tone,
столько сейчас экстра тоном будет
integration will definitely be a surf, in principle
интеграция безусловно серфом в принципе
it  there is already just need to be done for
она уже есть просто надо сделать для
tickets, respectively,
тикетов соответственно
in the same way, to sell, to bathe, to
точно также продавать купать производите
authorize any transactions,
авторизовать любые транзакции
respectively, it can be through depot, and
соответственно может быть через depot а
in the surf there
в серфе
will certainly be advanced analytics
будет безусловно расширенная аналитика
, here, as it were, potential, so to
вот здесь уже как бы потенциальный так
speak, bookmarks of various tokens that
сказать закладки различных токенов
are in various stages, that is,
находящихся в различных стадиях то есть
they are still on sale  with live
все таки находящиеся на продаже с живыми
offers without live offers and so on
офферами без живых офферов и так далее
, what's important is
вот что важно еще
that the platform allows you to create a talkin'
это платформа позволяет создать talkin'
here and now for anyone no in
здесь и сейчас любому человеку нет в
this sense there is no moderation, that
этом смысле нет никакой модерацию то
is, right now you can create they
есть прямо сейчас можно создать они
will be in a marvelous movie'
пробудут в дивны кино'
in a couple of days we are all  behind the
через там пару дней мы это все за за
trees,
деревьями
well, in principle, we simplified it  now the task is
ну в принципе мы упростили сейчас задачу
for the necklace so that they don’t
для для ожерелья для того чтобы они не
waste their tone and spend so far
тратили как бы свои тон и а тратили пока
only rubies
только рубинчики
on testing all this functionality
на тестирование всего этого функционала
after the approval of the competition,
после утверждения конкурса
respectively, it will all be hammered
соответственно это будет все забили
into mayonnaise and there any person
времена в майонез и там любой человек
will be able to create currents in which nuance we
сможет создать токи в чем нюанс мы
intend to produce  positive
предполагаем производить положительную
moderation not negative
модерацию не отрицательную
positive fight positive
положительному драться положительным
operation will mean that for the
операция будет означать что для от
model of equal auto authors or individual
модели равных авто авторов или отдельных
tops, we will have, let's say, expanded
топе нам будет скажем так расширенная
accessibility in the search,
доступность в поиске
respectively, any person entering
соответственно любой человек зайдя на
this platform will be able to choose whether he watches
эту платформу сможет выбрать он смотрит
only simulated content or the whole
только моделированы контент или весь
row, we understand that certainly not
подряд мы понимаем что безусловно не
moderated content can, let's say,
модерируемый контент может скажем так
there will be very magnus, but with one
там будет очень магнуса же одним
keystroke a person receives from
нажатием клавиши человек получает от
modeling content and can see
моделируя контент и может видеть
quality content from modeling
качественный контент от моделирование
verified and moreover, additionally
проверенный и более того дополнительно
there will be verification of authors and so
там будет верификация авторов и так
on, if necessary, of course, the
далее при необходимости конечно
next m  the moment with corresponding
следующий момент при соответственно
transactions now, when selling, our
транзакциях сейчас при продаже наша
platform
платформа
takes five percent there now, this
забирать там пять процентов сейчас это
is not indicated, but it was done a little on
не не указано но это сделано немножко
purpose, why, because we are now
специально почему потому что мы сейчас
working to complicate
работаем над тем чтобы усложнить
what commission structure it will be at
какую структуру комиссии она будет как
least three levels, that is, when
минимум трёх уровневая то есть при
creating a token and no longer  did the most
создании токена а уже не сделал самые
important created the top
главные создал топе
let's create it like this so
давайте создадим таким так давайте
let's pay attention to the trees
давайте про деревьев обращаю внимание
that when creating the top but I can
что при создании топе но я могу
connect any number of media files
подключить любое количество медиафайлов
and it will be all the same,
и это будет все один таким
respectively, this is a
соответственно это
flexible third triptych and so on, that
гибких третьими триптих и так далее то
is, in addition to the fact that just a series can be
есть помимо того что просто серию можно
created
создавать
accordingly  you can create and immediately
соответственно можно создавать и сразу
when creating a token,
при создании токена
I will restore for my beloved a commission
я восстановлю для себя любимого комиссию
that I want to receive a gift for life
которая хочу подарок получать пожизненно
from all sales of tokens, so I set,
со всех продаж токены вот я устанавливаю
let’s say 3 percent, but I won’t be here
допустим 3 процент вот но я не буду тут
very much
очень сильно
[music]
[музыка]
I wear our name accordingly
я ношу соответственно название
to tell our santa santa tau  for
нашу to tell нашу санту санта тау для
each of me files and  accordingly,
каждого из меня файлов и соответственно
yes, let's and we create a token, I pay for the
да давайте и мы создаем токен оплачиваю
creation of the top,
создание топе на
here we have created currents, let's
вот у нас создался токи давайте
look at it in yes, then here, but here it
посмотрим его в да потом здесь но здесь
shows from the first page,
показывает с первой страничке
respectively, that is, we have created a
соответственно то есть у нас создался
token about the commission, back to the
токен по поводу комиссии вернусь к
missions,
миссиям
why I listened and the creation of the docker,
почему я слушал и создание докера потому
because  when creating a token, you can set
что при создании токена можно задать
the creator’s commission, which will be
комиссию создателя которая будет
paid to the creator for all
выплачиваться создателю при всех
subsequent sales of who is a movie, and
последующих продаж кто кино и
accordingly, in addition to the creators’ commission
соответственно помимо комиссии создатели
, we have a commission fee in the platform,
у нас есть плат комиссия в платформы
it is fixed, the creator himself chooses
она фиксирована создатель сам выбирает
what size of commission he wants to
какой размер комиссии он хочет
set, he just needs to understand that
установить он просто должен понимать что
if he raises the commission, then  the liquidity of
если он комиссию завысить то ликвидность
such a token is sharply reduced, few people
такого токена резко снижается мало кто
want to
захочет
buy talkin' when selling
приобретать talkin' при продаже которого
which, we ask there, 20 or 30 percent of the
на просим там 20 или 30 процентов
cost always goes there to the owner
стоимости всегда уходят там собственнику
and the third type of commission that will be
и третий тип комиссии которая будет
used is the so-called showcase commission,
использоваться это комиссия так называем
that is, all these tokens they can be
витрины то есть эти все токены они могут
sold not only here on  uh  on that
продаваться не только здесь на этой
platform, they can be sold on any
платформе они могут продаваться в любом
site in any shop, and so on, and the
сайте в любом шопе и так далее и
creator of the token, return the seller, stand
создатель токена верни продавец стоите
on his own, assigns a commission that he is
на сам назначает комиссию которую он
ready to pay to the storefront, that is, and the
готов уплатить витрине то есть и чем
higher this percentage, the higher the commission, the
выше такой процент чем выше комиссии тем
more hunting, by the way, the storefronts will be
больше охота это кстати витрины будут
taken for sale
забирать на продажу
gives  such tokens, that is, the initiative for the
дает такие токены то есть инициатива за
distribution of
распространением
tokens, does not even fall on the
токенов ложится как бы ни даже не на
owner and maybe not even
собственника и не на может быть даже не
on us as on a platform, namely, showcases,
нас на как на платформу а именно витрины
that is, they are looking for interesting good currents,
то есть они ищут интересные хорошие токи
we have a good commission,
нас хороший комиссии
they are put up for sale,
их выставляют у себя на продажу
their own probably finished
собственная наверно закончил
thanks for the presentation so you are
спасибо за презентацию так тебя твоим
very limited who else would you like i'm
очень ограничено кто еще хотел бы я
ready for everyone hello i have a pen there
готов всем привет у меня ручка там
are some questions that may
какие-то вопросы на которые может быть
need someone to answer i just didn't
нужно кому-то ответить я просто не
follow so i'm in the chat 5 simple didn't take
следил так я в чате 5 простых не взял
me from us number eight  if, just in
меня у нас номер восемь если на всякий
case,
случай
our whip number eight guys immediately
наша плетей шим номер восемь ребят сразу
warn the last one for the presentation,
предупреждаю последний для презентации
because then it will happen only on
потому что потом доведется лишь на
sun  Unfortunately, I’m wasting time there, the post office
встречу к сожалению время там почта
borders the guys Alexander, so let’s
граничит ребят александр вот давай
try to get up, let’s then
постараемся пор по подняться давай тогда
control the crane once very quickly, but I
управление краном раз очень быстро но
’ll just have to gallop across Europe
придется просто галопом по европам
dandelion eyes free I
одуванчик eyes free
switch to Russian then since we have
перехожу на русский тогда раз у нас
very little time I was one of the
совсем мало времени я был одним из
participants in the competition for tickets to  dubai
участников конкурса на билеты в дубае
took first place and went went there
занял первое место и поехала поехал туда
and I presented this presentation,
и я презентовал вот эту презентацию я
then I throw off the whole chat, it will probably be
тогда скидывай весь чат наверное будет
more convenient if you just scroll through it yourself,
удобнее если просто вы пролистаете сами
we’ll see there’s no time to tell,
посмотрим уже нет времени рассказывать
I’ll probably stop only on our
наверное остановлюсь только на нашем
positioning of our solution and
позиционирование нашего решения и
immediately transferred the time to the developer at
переданы сразу время разработчику хотя
least to show a little  the service
бы чтобы немножко показал на сервис
is not completely cast ideal,
полностью не каст идеальный таким
so this is a decentralized solution,
образом это децентрализованное решения
everything is based on smart contracts inside the
все на смарт-контракты внутри блокчейна
blockchain and but otherwise it’s necessary, maybe I’ll
и но иначе ственный надо же может быть и
turn it on
включу
so that I can be seen and demonstrate
чтобы меня было видно и демонстрацию
the launch screen,
экрана запуска
so the spot screen please tell me
так экран пятна скажите пожалуйста то
that something is not displayed, it seems to me a
что то не то отображается мне кажется
presentation  mine is visible no no  no no
презентация мои видно нет нет нет нет не
wrong screen screen
так экран экран
presentation turns out to be in general about
презентация оказывается в общем про
positioning
позиционирование
not a test perfect service built by a
не тест идеальный сервис построены
runny tractor we paid special
насморком трактор мы особый уделять
attention to
уделили внимание
evaluating the advantages of rhyton blockchains
оценив преимущества блокчейнов ритон
over other blockchains such as
перед другими блокчейн ими такие как
ethereum on which the majority
эфириум на котором большинство
in the market place of and these market
in the market place of and эти market
place of spins understood  that the high
place of крутится поняли что высокая
transaction speed is the most important
скорость транзакции самое главное
high speed of execution of smart
высокая скорость исполнения smart
contracts and low commission is the main
контрактов и низкая комиссия основное
advantage and it is quite possible that we will
преимущество и вполне возможно мы
attract an audience that was
привлечем к аудиторию которая была
inaccessible to the blockchain like the ethereum and
недоступна блокчейна как эфириум и
something obvious like this fruit it is the
чего-то очевидного как это fruit он
community
комьюнити
so these are the authors and creators who are
так это авторы и создатели которые
worried about the safety of their work  what
беспокоятся о безопасности их работ что
we mean in this case, we
мы в данном случае имеем ввиду у нас
have the option the user will choose
есть опция пользователь будет выбирать
where he wants to store files either in the
где он хочет хранить файлы либо в
blockchain
блокчейне
or on and tfs if he stores on pfs then
либо на и tfs если он хранит на pfs то
a hash is made on this file and placed
делается хэш на данный файл и помещается
in and when he talked into this more
в and when he talked into this more
contract rays
контракт лучи
if  he stores the blockchain then he uploads
если он хранит блокчейне то он загружает
full file block whose here we have
полностью файл блок чей вот у нас есть
white paper
white paper
I will send it a link now before there are
я его сейчас пришлю ссылку перед есть
calculations including the cost well
расчеты в том числе и по стоимости ну
how much the file will be stored in the blockchain
сколько будет хранить файл в блокчейне
I will send it probably I put 50
отправлю его наверное я положил 50
telegram fridon and cities of gardens
телеграмма фридон and cities of gardens
also on the first page link to
также на первой же странице ссылка на
github
github
like this, if we are talking about the
вот таким образом если мы говорим про
target audience, and also these are games or
целевую аудиторию а также это игры или
various sports, gaming, gambling, that is,
различные спорт гейминг гемблинг то есть
those for which it is important to quickly execute
те которых важно быстрое исполнение
transactions and sell, for example, some kind of
транзакций и продажа например каких-то
incity
incity
artifact inside the presentation, you
артефакта внутри презентации достаточно
can see this in detail, you can
подробно об этом сказано можете
see it, well, as an example for yourself
посмотреть это ну как бы пример сам
marketplace we have it in a state of
marketplace у нас он в состоянии
well you and even loudly say the state of
ну вы и даже громко сказать состоянии
beta versions we have fully
бета-версий у нас готовы полностью
smart contracts ready, including
смарт-контракты включая
placing files on the blockchain and calling them
помещение файлов на блокчейн и вызов их
from there, this is just the developers will show
оттуда это как раз разработчики покажет
in terms of design we were very
с точки зрения дизайна мы сильно
late because we tried to make it
задержались потому что старались сделать
as fast as possible
максимально
solution and its for friendly we
скоростное решение и ее за френдли мы
tried to integrate with extra tons
пытались интегрироваться с экстра тонн
on  an example when we log in here and
например когда мы здесь логинимся и
enter extra done
входим в экстра done
but without any security protection it immediately
но без всякой защиты по сэйфти он сразу
performs integration, but if we
производит интеграцию но если мы
try to create a collection for us,
попытаемся создать коллекцию для нас
at first the collection is the placement of a smart
вначале коллекция это помещение smart
contract hands a
контракта руки контракт
blockchain contract and then the candy rally
блокчейн а дальше уже митинг конфеты
takes place inside these rings and inside
происходит внутри этих колец и внутри
smart contracts  and that is why we
smart контрактов и именно поэтому мы
can continue to provide high speed,
дальше можем обеспечить высокую скорость
but in fact one game can create
но фактически одна игра может создать
its own mouth smart contracts continue to screw
свой рот смарт-контракты дальше винтить
inside the morning already in an unlimited
внутри утра уже в неограниченном
number of dockers,
количестве докера
but the extra one cannot, for a diploma,
но экстра тот не может за диплом
smart contracts can execute operations,
смарт-контракты может исполнять операции
and a diploma is not hanging around, we
наметить а диплом не шляется ребятам мы
tied the guys  with them they admitted that yes there is
связали с ними они признали что да есть
such a problem and we need to solve it and we
такой задачи и надо решить и мы
agreed that by the end of the week they will
договорились чтобы конца недели они ее
do it and thus we
сделают и таким образом у нас возможно
will probably have a user friendly to do everything through an
будет юзер френдли делать все через
extra house and we talked about the reset, we will
экстра дом и мы переговорили сброса мы
connect them to tons of felling which you 3
подключим их тонн валят который вы 3
supports the browser on  also an extension
поддерживает браузер на тоже расширение
and start doing it
и начну это делать
you bot will be the next step  I’m
ты бот будет следующим шагом мне сейчас
already finished now, it will appear
уже закончиться вот появится позже
later, respectively, the creation of a collection
вот соответственно создание коллекции
after that inside the rings and mehndi tokens,
после этого внутри колец и менди токенов
and at the moment we can
и у нас на настоящий момент возможно
create a collection that is, for heat from the
создать коллекцию то есть за тепло из
mark through only through tons of sdk
марка through только через тонн sdk
through just about mnemonics and further
через вот-вот мнемоники и дальнейшем
further already work with for  a diploid
дальнейшем уже работа с за диплоидным
smart contract is already possible and through extra
smart контракта можно уже и через экстра
the roman please switch to the
the roman переключи пожалуйста на
developers let it just show
разработчиков пусть он просто покажет
more specifically stop the screen installed
уже конкретней останови screen установил
[music]
[музыка]
show you how you can pick up the file
показать вам как можно подобрать файл
right now we can see on the screen
прямо сейчас мы можем видеть на экране
this address where this is a cruel contract and
этот адрес куда это жестоким контракт и
here we can already close  this file now
сюда можно уже закрыть этот файл сейчас
it works only through my cry and
это работает только через мой крик и вот
here andre lends itself to the file name i did
здесь поддаются андре имя файла я сделал
i want to upload a lot of our
я хочу загрузить много нашего
marketplace show as soon as find
маркетплейса покажи как только найди
7 because already in others are busy between
7 потому что уже в другие заняты между
you can specify any type this is for different
можете указать любой тип это для разных
types i.e. you can upload videos
типов то есть можно быть загружать видео
under flexible so that they demonstrate and the
под гибкий чтобы они демонстрируют и
capture of a foreign car is easier
захват иномарки проще
to feel
ощущать отображается
it’s a leg to wait a little because we have
это нога чуть подождать потому что у нас
an average download of jason we
какая среднем загрузка джейсон мы
rewrote the file they fed something that
переписали они файла у питали то что
somewhere in fact a kilobyte for 5 seconds, well, that
где-то ведь килобайт на 5 секунд ну то
is, colleagues of the present to them rather
есть коллеги настоящего им достаточно
slowly, yes, that is, if someone wants to
медленно да то есть если кто то захочет
place their picture 0 5 megabytes  then
поместить свою картину 0 5 мегабайт то
it’s quite reasonable if it has a good
вполне разумно если у него хорошее
resolution, well, you’ll have to visit it for
разрешение ну придется посетить минут
a few minutes, but in principle it
там подождать но в принципе достаточно
works quite stably in the next version,
стабильно работает в следующей версии
we’ll already have a resume done, at
уже будет у нас докачка сделано вот на
the moment it’s happening more often,
настоящий момент чаще это происходит
success sex, here we successfully wander the
секс успеха вот у нас успешно забредет
file is shown here by methods for
файл здесь показывается методами для
this  this is the size of this file, that
этого есть это у нас размер это файл то
is, logically 6 kilobytes, such yuri
есть 6 по логике килобайт таким юрий
yuri
юрий
there are two types of data about such yuri, they
есть два типа данных о таком юрия то
can specify another additional method
могут указать еще дополнительный методом
and this one can play just a
и еще данный могут играть просто
blockchain, you can kill it that if we
блокчейн можно убить это что если
refresh the page with this wallet and
обновим страницу с этим кошельком и
we can see that  the balance has changed and
можем увидеть это что баланс изменился и
to that
к что
about 0.6 crystals it cost downloading 50
около 0,6 кристалла стоило загрузка 50
50 6 kilobytes the matron file was successfully
50 6 килобайт файл матроны успешную
loaded  the problem is that it takes so
загрузился проблема в том что он так
long to conclude because now there is a
долго заключать потому что сейчас есть
limit to the office plus 0 was originally
ограничение в офис плюс 0 изначально
within the usual tone it is 8
была в течение у обычного тона это 8
club
club
it has now been raised to 16 kilobytes,
его сейчас притом подняли до 16 килобайт
I hope that it is precisely transactions and the
я надеюсь то что именно и транзакции и
return of
отдача
data about these dance countries will be
данных об этих стран танцев будет
increased  next time
увеличена в следующий раз
drag that will allow you to upload
тащите что позволит быстрее загружать
files faster directly to the barrel and when you are
файлы прямо в бочину а когда ты
property what downloads the generalization of
имущество то что загружает обобщение
decentralization that this file
децентрализации то что этот файл никак
cannot be done and you can always get it
не поделать и его всегда можно получить
and in communication this is the main thing that
и в общении этому это основное то что
[music]
[музыка]
so I x when completely  will be
таким образом я x когда полностью будет
ready to create a collection
готов создание коллекции
after this rally ft through tons of sdk
после этого митинга ft через тонн sdk
or export it or fire the
или экспорт он или уволит кристалла
process crystal and place it on the auction for
процесса и помещение на аукцион на
auction and direct sale we work
аукцион и прямую продажу нас работает
one smart contract just in one fixed price the
один smart контракт просто в одном цена
other is the
фиксированных другом это
bits of the rate who interrupts it himself and the
биты ставки кто самим ее перебивает и
choice of premises or blockchain  file, or
выбор помещения либо блокчейн файла либо
here is the functionality that
вот вот тот функционал который на
is currently implemented on smart
настоящий момент реализован на смарт
contracts and will  Wicks is reflected
контрактах и будет отражен
, which is now defective, everything
викс который сейчас неполноценным все
is so short in order to keep up, well, there
так вот коротко чтобы успевать ну вот в
was a question in the chat, I kind of like this is exactly how
чате были вопрос я вроде вот именно так
this face is,
это лицо
and
а
thank you very much for the presentation,
спасибо большое за презентацию очень
it’s very difficult, I wanted to move on to the next
сложно вот хотел перейти к следующему
speaker,
спикеру
so bevan, who, yes, thank you very much, was
так беван которая да спасибо большое был
here for a very long time, yes, I’ll try  it won’t
очень долго тут да я постараюсь точно не
take long for sure
занять много времени
hello everyone I will also talk in
всем привет я тоже буду рассказывать на
Russian
русском
my name is Ivan Karpukhin we represent
меня зовут иван карпухин мы представляем
13 tires themselves also my colleagues are participating in the meeting
13 сами шин также во встрече участвуют
who will then answer the
мои коллеги которые потом ответят на
question on the technical part
вопрос по технической части
now I will expand the screen the best
сейчас я расширю экран лучшая
presentation is our finished product and I
презентация это наш готовый продукт и
’ll just walk quietly  in order
пройдусь просто потихонечку по порядку
from top to bottom and so this is our marketplace
сверху вниз и так это наш marketplace
grand bazaar this is probably a classic
гранд базар это наверное классический
marketplace in the current understanding of the trend
маркетплейс в текущих пониманиях тренда
that is, we allow any artist to post
то есть мы позволяем размещать любым
any material we have
артистом любые материал у нас нет
no restrictions it can be
никаких ограничений это могут быть
coins it can be seen it can
монеты это может быть видел это может
be an image a ticket and in general everything that
быть изображение билет и вообще все что
whatever the only thing is that there is no
угодно единственное что пока нету
support
поддержки
yet  dio above, we are now showing that we
аудио сверху мы сейчас показываем что мы
are working on a test network and you need to spend
работаем в тестовой сети и тратить нужно
rubies, well, let's go the registration process
рубинчики ну и погнали процесс
,
регистрации
registration is now possible in two
регистрация возможна сейчас двумя
ways, it's either connecting via
способами это либо подключение через
google or via the hop guide, we
google либо через гид хоп мы
registered through an extra volume,
зарегистрировались через экстра том
my wallet was connected,
подсоединился мой кошелечек
you can check the address and now you can
можно сверить адрес и теперь можно
start interacting  here we have
начать взаимодействия здесь у нас
a starting guide for working with the
расположен стартовый гайд по работе с
platform, in fact, it just
платформой на самом деле там просто
tells where to get the extension of the fire in
рассказывает где взять расширение костра
tone, how to get test
тоном как через как получить тестовые
rubies
рубинчики
and in general what it is, it’s completely for
и вообще что это такое это уж совсем для
users who are far from
пользователей которые далеки от всей
this whole story, then we see the collections I
этой истории дальше мы видим коллекции я
won’t  to explain what it is already
не буду объяснять что это такое уже
repeatedly said we can fall
неоднократно говорили можем провалиться
into any of them goes the name of the collection
в любую из них идет название коллекции
description of the collection what is currently
описание коллекции то что сейчас в
on sale in the collection at
коллекции находится на продаже на
the moment this is the entire collection that is,
текущий момент это вся коллекция то есть
some things may not be sold
некоторые вещи могут не продаваться
well, of course, as the creator of this
ну естественно я как создатель этой
collection, I can edit the cover
коллекции могу отредактировать обложку
the description of the name and that's anything
описание названия и это все что угодно
else, this is directly what
дальше это непосредственно то что
recently appeared on the Theisse brand
недавно из нового появилось на марке
, we can filter by girls
тайссе мы можем отфильтровать по девкам
by image by video as I said
по изображением по видео как я сказал
earlier audio will be added a little later
ранее аудио добавится чуть позже
below we see the statistics of the platform, that
ниже мы видим статистику платформы то
is, now these are top buyers these are
есть сейчас это топовые покупателя это
top artists  the sellers are the largest
топовые артисты продавцы самые большие
collections, therefore, from the tops by the
коллекции поэтому из топы по
collector, here I am, top cheers, now the
коллекционером вот я топ ура теперь
process, well, the purchase can be shown right away,
процесс ну покупка можно сразу показать
in fact, so as not to wait a second,
на самом деле чтобы не тянуть секундочку
here I will fall into the collection, let’s say, by the
вот я провалюсь в коллекцию допустим
way, this
кстати это
canta here we see the product itself, we see
канта здесь мы видим сам продукт видим
which collection belongs to who is now the
какой коллекция относится кто сейчас
owner of it who  creator cost there are
владелец ее кто создатель стоимость есть
slight delays not related to us everything
небольшие задержки связаны не с нами все
I automatically became the owner the
я стал автоматически владельцем остался
old
старый
creator remained and I already have this work from the collection,
создатель и у меня из коллекции есть уже
then I can fall
вот эта работа дальше я могу провалиться
into my profile here I got from the
в свой профиль вот у меня появилась от
work it is not for
работы она сейчас не выставлен на
sale now I can put it up  at any
продажу я могу ее выставить в любой
time
момент
for how much we bought it,
за сколько мы ее купили
no matter you  you work, I write down
неважно вы заработаете я прописываю
how many crystals I want to see here
сколько кристалликов я хочу вижу здесь
fi service and how much I will get everything
сервис fi и сколько я получу все
please it is now for sale
пожалуйста она сейчас выставлен на
so more about
так подробнее еще об аккаунте
my account this is
моим это
what I created these are my tokens that I
что я создал это мои токена которые я
created through the platform some of them are
создал через платформу часть из них
for sale part no this is what I
продается часть нет это то что я
I collect here there are also items of
коллекционирую здесь есть также предметы
other artists, this is all that I sell,
других артистов это все что я продаю
respectively, filters work everywhere,
соответственно фильтры везде работают
anyone can go to my page and
любой может зайти на мою страничку и
see what’s going on with me in general,
посмотреть что у меня вообще происходит
I can also edit the appearance,
также могу отредактировать внешний вид
add a description, change the name, you can
добавить описание поменять имя можно
demonstrate, I just
продемонстрировать просто временное
don’t want to waste time and, accordingly,
тратить не хочется и соответственно
mail for notifications
почта для уведомлений
so now here are a couple of moments and I
так теперь еще вот пару моментов и
’ll show you how to create a subscription form
покажу создания форма подписки на то
to prevent the drop and because it’s
чтобы не подпускать дроп и потому что
clear that when we enter my network
понятно что когда мы выйдем в моей сеть
we will have our own collection
у нас будет своя коллекция
directly from the grand bazaar, plus we
непосредственно от гранд базара плюс мы
connect third-party artists and so that the
подключаем сторонних артистов и чтобы
user can understand what
пользователь во время мог понять что
something interesting appeared  det
появилось что-то интересно он будет
pavich to receive a notification further,
павич получать уведомление дальше
even though it’s their vipe, well, we seem to have a good
хоть это им випе ну мы как бы с неплохим
experience in creating products and we are
опытом создания продуктов и мы все
trying to do everything for the user, we
стараемся делать для пользователя у нас
have a hold center here is just a
есть hold центр здесь как раз расположен
beginner guide and now we are starting
beginner гайд и вот мы сейчас начинаем
to collect a collection of help of now I’m
собирать коллекцию help of сейчас я
right in the morning  I will open all the links,
сразу с утра открою все ссылочки очень
it seems to me very important for users and
важно мне кажется для пользователей и
the chain belly that we have been running
the chain живот который мы ведем с
since entering the competition every day we
момента выхода на конкурс ежедневно у
have changes and judges any
нас происходит изменения и судьи любые
other users can come in the evening
другие пользователи могут вечером
and understand what happened
заходите и понимать что у нас произошло
so further feedback is also important,
так далее фидбэк тоже немаловажное
it is in some way a support  here you can
это в некотором роде саппорт здесь можно
leave here you can leave information
оставить здесь можно оставить информацию
about the gods, report content or just
о богах зарепортить контент или просто
place some general wishes, well,
какие-то общие пожелания разместить ну
that’s understandable social networks, we are just starting
это понятно социалки мы только начинаем
to develop, so now the limit to creating is
развивать так теперь предел к созданию
playing digital lighting which we want to
играем digital lighting которых хотим
place, by the way, it doesn’t have
разместить ну кстати он не обязательно
to be something, that is, it’s just
должен быть что то есть это просто
an image that will already
изображение которое уже к чему-то там
be attached to something there  let's go preview how
будет привязан увидим превьюшку того как
our talking will look like an important
будет выглядеть наш talking важный
moment we can just create it and not
момент мы можем просто его создать и не
put it up for sale or we can immediately
выставлять на продажу а можем сразу
put it up for sale put 100
поставить на продажу поставим 100
crystals the choice of a collection you can
кристалликов выбор коллекции можно
choose this my collection I can
выбрать вот эту моя коллекция могу
place an existing one this way I can create a new one
разместить эту таким могу создать новую
let's create a new name description
давайте создадим новое название описание
Kirill is whoever is there as he wishes the
кирилл это кто там как пожелает
collection has appeared so I choose the
коллекция появилась вот я выбираю
placement in it now we are moving on
размещение в ней теперь мы переходим уже
to the description of our Tokyo but I don’t really
к описанию нашего токио но я не очень
like such knives test things
люблю такие ножи тестовые вещи так
to call so on in time no and create this
называть на во времени нет и создаем эту
we warn here that we take a
мы предупреждаем здесь что мы берем
small commission back in  05 crystals and
небольшую комиссию еще в 05 кристаллов и
then we return it, in fact, it is
потом возвращаем ее фактически она
frozen now, let's look sometimes and it
замораживается сейчас посмотрим иногда и
can fail for the test network if suddenly
за тестовой сети может сбоить если вдруг
something does not work, I will create for on
что-то не пройдет я создам за на
but again, all the tokens with which everything is
но опять же все токены которыми все
fine, everyone here appeared our
хорошо всем вот появился наш таким
description of the cost, I can withdraw at any time
описание стоимость я в любой момент могу
its from the sale binding to the collection the
снять его с продажи привязка к коллекции
owner and creator are still such a mini
владелец и создатель еще такие мини
mom  ents can like items then it
моменты можно лайкать предметы потом это
will appear in favorites favorites
будет появляться в избранном избранное
will be in the profile of each
будет находиться в профиле каждого
user, that is, a
пользователя то есть вот здесь появится
tab will appear here, probably from the general moments
вкладочка вот наверное из общих моментов
all that are not now there are auctions but they
все чего сейчас нет это аукционов но их
are not directly on the platform today
нет непосредственно на платформе сегодня
we have Tuesday I think that Thursday is the
у нас вторник я думаю что четверг
last Friday  the auction will already be here
крайтом пятница аукцион уже будут здесь
and it will be possible to use them further, well, it’s clear
и можно будет их юзать дальше ну понятно
that the possibility of connecting in a year
что возможность коннекта через год тоже
will also be, but probably already after the competition
будет но наверное уже после конкурса
now any technical questions
сейчас любые технические вопросы мне на
will help me answer them Ivan cousins and Yaroslav Yu
них помогут ответить иван кузины и
ina these are our technical specialists
ярослав юдина это наши технические
guys who drank backend, we
специалисты ребята которые пили backend
l, I’m ready  in principle,
вот ну я готов мне в принципе все
everything fell asleep to
все заснули
me, did I understand that, or did they just open the mouth of the
я что же так понял или или просто рот
chips, how cool are the colleagues have
открыли чипы как круто вот коллеги есть
any questions at all the presentation of the
какие-нибудь вопросы на всех презентация
spire should be in the cockpit, both just that is,
шпиля должны кабине оба просто то есть я
I can once again know, I asked the
что еще раз могу скорее знаете я задал
question lol login via  here is google yes or
вопрос лон логин через вот google да или
no to what it is for what is the purpose what is the goal
нет к он для чего нужен какая вот цель
in order to far  it’s better to develop an
какая для того чтобы дальше развивать
ecosystem of users, this turns out to be a
экосистему пользователей это получается
personal account,
личная учетка
that is, people should continue to
то есть люди должны дальше
communicate with themselves, like
коммуницировать вместе с собой лайкать
each other, send tokens to each other,
друг друга отправлять друг другу токена
and so on, this is a social story, that is, the
и прочее это социальная история то есть
question is if it’s implemented this way, it’s
вопрос если почему так реализован это
different for what onion how for what in
другая для чего лука как для чего для
order for social history to
того чтобы социальная история
develop  of course, this is a marketplace,
развивалась конечно это же marketplace
this is done primarily for people
это делается в первую очередь для людей
people want to put up for sale their oh
люди хотят выставлять на продажу свои ой
there and other people want to buy
там и другие люди хотят покупать
collect resell and so
коллекционировать перепродавать и так
on there must be some kind of communication
далее должно быть какая-то коммуникация
between them I ended up through google then
между ними меня закончился через google
connect and roles and not say what
дальше connect и роли и не говорить что
u  you will have such an address, it’s as
у вас будет вот такой то адрес это как
if it’s being created in your north, why
бы создается у вас на севере нет почему
is it that it pulls up the address of the wallet in the
это он подтягивает адрес кошелька язык
stratton language, and the one that I have now for
stratton а тот который у меня сейчас за
lags
лаги
yes, of course, the following, that is, when we
да конечно следующее то есть когда мы
connect the wallet
подключаем кошелек
than the wallet like stratton, we take seiner
чем кошелек как stratton мы берем seiner
extra tone and  with through our root
экстра тона и с через уже наш рутовый
contract, which sets the elevator
контракт который задает лифте
wallets  then we take it on cyan, well, that
кошельки просто берем на циане ну то
is, a public rivotek of a person and you can
есть паблик rivotek человека и можно
use the stratton language and create on this
язык stratton и создаем на этом
basis
основании
people a peel, that is, you yourself and bring it on, we
люди кожуру то есть сами и приводите мы
won’t have any earlier, we take the
не будем иметь никаких ранее мы берем
already existing Crimeas are turned off or,
уже существующие крыма выключаются или а
personally, yes, I forgot to show it is
лично да вот еще забыл показать еще в
definitely underway  history, that is, when
безусловно ведется история то есть когда
and by whom it was created, how it was
и кем была создана как таким было
bought, well, you can watch it thanks to a
куплено ну вот можно смотреть благодарен
colleague
коллеге
separately, I would also like to ask the
отдельно еще хотелось бы попросить
judges who will later watch this
судьи которые будут потом смотреть эту
record or they are present now,
запись либо они присутствуют сейчас
please register to
очень просим регистрироваться
use it and do not be shy to ask
пользоваться и не стесняться задавать
questions, that is, we can say with confidence
вопросы то есть мы с уверенностью можем
that we have a finished product and
сказать что у нас готовый продукт и
you can even create a resell in the test,
можно даже в тесте создавать
I don’t know, maybe we will
перепродавать я не знаю может быть мы
launch some kind of gamification and
запустим какую-то геймификация и там
then there will be prizes for a top buyer, a village
потом будут призы топовым байером селе
frame, and so on, so don’t be
раму и так далее вот поэтому не
shy to use it and ask your
стесняйтесь пользуйтесь и задавать
colleagues a question, are you really all asleep,
вопрос коллеги ты реально все спят
and if
а если просто надеюсь надеюсь мы тоже
i just hope i
онут страничка x пор еще если только но
hope we too  about the whole marketplace is already
опять же это весь marketplace уже
directly
непосредственно
here, that is, here everything is absolute darkness,
вот то есть здесь все абсолютной тьмы
which are also filtered from by price by
которые также фильтруются от по цене по
cost by what you can buy
стоимости по тому что можно купить
now
сейчас
and, accordingly, by type, so
ну и соответственно уже по типам вот
if there are no questions, I probably have all
если вопросов нет наверное у меня все
thanks for the presentation of a very good
спасибо за презентацию очень хорошей
presentation of the guys to all of you very much
презентации ребят всем вам большое
thank
огромное спасибо за то что вы выступили
you so much for submitting those works, if suddenly one of the
с теми работами вот если вдруг кто-то из
participants did not have time to join
участников не успел присоединиться к
this one, and massasi, he can send a video
этой а массаси он может прислать видео
that will be later for the rest of the participants.
которое будет потом остальным участникам
this night and wanted to say
вот на эту ночь и хотел сказать всем
thank you very much to everyone, and now it will be literally
спасибо большое а сейчас будет буквально
in 50 minutes of daily meetings, but
через 50 минут ежедневных встреч а вот
thanks to everyone, see you soon everyone bye
всем спасибо до скорых встреч всем пока